{"RT_log_version":"1.0.1","RT_log_data":[{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946791070904","data":{"timestamp":" 946791070904"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_083053"," gameId":" 9f84d7c3-359f-41e3-b7a2-1cc48ab0b959"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MBUGA"," userResponse":" MBUGA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946791071127","data":{"timestamp":" 946791071126"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_083053"," gameId":" 9f84d7c3-359f-41e3-b7a2-1cc48ab0b959"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZA"," userResponse":" ZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946791072090","data":{"timestamp":" 946791072090"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_083053"," gameId":" 9f84d7c3-359f-41e3-b7a2-1cc48ab0b959"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WANYAMA"," userResponse":" WANYAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946791073363","data":{"timestamp":" 946791073363"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_083053"," gameId":" 9f84d7c3-359f-41e3-b7a2-1cc48ab0b959"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TANZANIA"," userResponse":" TANZANIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946791076208","data":{"timestamp":" 946791076208"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_083053"," gameId":" 9f84d7c3-359f-41e3-b7a2-1cc48ab0b959"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946791077051","data":{"timestamp":" 946791077051"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_083053"," gameId":" 9f84d7c3-359f-41e3-b7a2-1cc48ab0b959"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWANZA"," userResponse":" KWANZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946791077364","data":{"timestamp":" 946791077364"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_083053"," gameId":" 9f84d7c3-359f-41e3-b7a2-1cc48ab0b959"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946791078596","data":{"timestamp":" 946791078596"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_083053"," gameId":" 9f84d7c3-359f-41e3-b7a2-1cc48ab0b959"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SERENGETI"," userResponse":" SERENGETI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946791082089","data":{"timestamp":" 946791082089"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_083053"," gameId":" 9f84d7c3-359f-41e3-b7a2-1cc48ab0b959"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngorongoro Manyara na Mikumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NGORONGORO"," userResponse":" NGORONGORO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946791083073","data":{"timestamp":" 946791083073"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_083053"," gameId":" 9f84d7c3-359f-41e3-b7a2-1cc48ab0b959"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngorongoro Manyara na Mikumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MANYARA"," userResponse":" MANYARA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946791083326","data":{"timestamp":" 946791083326"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_083053"," gameId":" 9f84d7c3-359f-41e3-b7a2-1cc48ab0b959"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngorongoro Manyara na Mikumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946791084268","data":{"timestamp":" 946791084268"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_083053"," gameId":" 9f84d7c3-359f-41e3-b7a2-1cc48ab0b959"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngorongoro Manyara na Mikumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MIKUMI"," userResponse":" MIKUMI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946791087095","data":{"timestamp":" 946791087095"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_083053"," gameId":" 9f84d7c3-359f-41e3-b7a2-1cc48ab0b959"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" O"," userResponse":" O"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946791088127","data":{"timestamp":" 946791088127"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_083053"," gameId":" 9f84d7c3-359f-41e3-b7a2-1cc48ab0b959"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TANZANIA"," userResponse":" TANZANIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946791088602","data":{"timestamp":" 946791088602"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_083053"," gameId":" 9f84d7c3-359f-41e3-b7a2-1cc48ab0b959"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" OYEE"," userResponse":" OYEE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946791093104","data":{"timestamp":" 946791093104"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_083053"," gameId":" 9f84d7c3-359f-41e3-b7a2-1cc48ab0b959"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" songs"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946791093175","data":{"timestamp":" 946791093175"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_083053"," gameId":" 9f84d7c3-359f-41e3-b7a2-1cc48ab0b959"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" OYEE"," userResponse":" OYEE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946791098678","data":{"timestamp":" 946791098678"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_083053"," gameId":" 9f84d7c3-359f-41e3-b7a2-1cc48ab0b959"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" songs"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946791131169","data":{"timestamp":" 946791131168"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_083053"," gameId":" 22d86f6a-68d1-40a1-87ed-2249606fb538"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_39"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ninasubiri teksi na mamangu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HUJAMBO"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946791133204","data":{"timestamp":" 946791133204"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_083053"," gameId":" 22d86f6a-68d1-40a1-87ed-2249606fb538"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_39"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ninasubiri teksi na mamangu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HUJAMBO"," userResponse":" HUJAMBO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946791136311","data":{"timestamp":" 946791136311"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_083053"," gameId":" 22d86f6a-68d1-40a1-87ed-2249606fb538"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_39"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ninasubiri teksi na mamangu."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JINA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946791138102","data":{"timestamp":" 946791138102"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_083053"," gameId":" 22d86f6a-68d1-40a1-87ed-2249606fb538"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_39"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ninasubiri teksi na mamangu."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LANGU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946791139810","data":{"timestamp":" 946791139810"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_083053"," gameId":" 22d86f6a-68d1-40a1-87ed-2249606fb538"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_39"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ninasubiri teksi na mamangu."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946791141759","data":{"timestamp":" 946791141759"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_083053"," gameId":" 22d86f6a-68d1-40a1-87ed-2249606fb538"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_39"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ninasubiri teksi na mamangu."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NANU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946791143313","data":{"timestamp":" 946791143313"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_083053"," gameId":" 22d86f6a-68d1-40a1-87ed-2249606fb538"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_39"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ninasubiri teksi na mamangu."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JINA"," userResponse":" JINA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946791143747","data":{"timestamp":" 946791143747"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_083053"," gameId":" 22d86f6a-68d1-40a1-87ed-2249606fb538"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_39"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ninasubiri teksi na mamangu."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LANGU"," userResponse":" LANGU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946791143941","data":{"timestamp":" 946791143941"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_083053"," gameId":" 22d86f6a-68d1-40a1-87ed-2249606fb538"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_39"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ninasubiri teksi na mamangu."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946791144445","data":{"timestamp":" 946791144445"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_083053"," gameId":" 22d86f6a-68d1-40a1-87ed-2249606fb538"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_39"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ninasubiri teksi na mamangu."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NANU"," userResponse":" NANU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946791148198","data":{"timestamp":" 946791148198"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_083053"," gameId":" 22d86f6a-68d1-40a1-87ed-2249606fb538"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_39"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ninasubiri teksi na mamangu."," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NINASUBIRI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946791149914","data":{"timestamp":" 946791149913"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_083053"," gameId":" 22d86f6a-68d1-40a1-87ed-2249606fb538"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_39"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ninasubiri teksi na mamangu."," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TEKSI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946791151641","data":{"timestamp":" 946791151641"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_083053"," gameId":" 22d86f6a-68d1-40a1-87ed-2249606fb538"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_39"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ninasubiri teksi na mamangu."," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946791153623","data":{"timestamp":" 946791153622"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_083053"," gameId":" 22d86f6a-68d1-40a1-87ed-2249606fb538"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_39"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ninasubiri teksi na mamangu."," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAMANGU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946791155803","data":{"timestamp":" 946791155802"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_083053"," gameId":" 22d86f6a-68d1-40a1-87ed-2249606fb538"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_39"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ninasubiri teksi na mamangu."," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NINASUBIRI"," userResponse":" NINASUBIRI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946791156389","data":{"timestamp":" 946791156389"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_083053"," gameId":" 22d86f6a-68d1-40a1-87ed-2249606fb538"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_39"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ninasubiri teksi na mamangu."," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TEKSI"," userResponse":" TEKSI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946791156581","data":{"timestamp":" 946791156581"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_083053"," gameId":" 22d86f6a-68d1-40a1-87ed-2249606fb538"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_39"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ninasubiri teksi na mamangu."," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946791157345","data":{"timestamp":" 946791157345"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_083053"," gameId":" 22d86f6a-68d1-40a1-87ed-2249606fb538"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_39"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ninasubiri teksi na mamangu."," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAMANGU"," userResponse":" MAMANGU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946791160418","data":{"timestamp":" 946791160418"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_083053"," gameId":" 22d86f6a-68d1-40a1-87ed-2249606fb538"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_39"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tunaenda nyumbani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TUNAENDA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946791162476","data":{"timestamp":" 946791162475"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_083053"," gameId":" 22d86f6a-68d1-40a1-87ed-2249606fb538"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_39"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tunaenda nyumbani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYUMBANI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946791164397","data":{"timestamp":" 946791164396"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_083053"," gameId":" 22d86f6a-68d1-40a1-87ed-2249606fb538"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_39"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tunaenda nyumbani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TUNAENDA"," userResponse":" TUNAENDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946791165182","data":{"timestamp":" 946791165181"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_083053"," gameId":" 22d86f6a-68d1-40a1-87ed-2249606fb538"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_39"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tunaenda nyumbani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYUMBANI"," userResponse":" NYUMBANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946791170560","data":{"timestamp":" 946791170560"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_083053"," gameId":" 22d86f6a-68d1-40a1-87ed-2249606fb538"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_39"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mamangu ananiimbia wimbo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HAPA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946791172712","data":{"timestamp":" 946791172712"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_083053"," gameId":" 22d86f6a-68d1-40a1-87ed-2249606fb538"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_39"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mamangu ananiimbia wimbo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NIMESIMAMA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946791174364","data":{"timestamp":" 946791174364"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_083053"," gameId":" 22d86f6a-68d1-40a1-87ed-2249606fb538"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_39"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mamangu ananiimbia wimbo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWENYE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946791176892","data":{"timestamp":" 946791176892"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_083053"," gameId":" 22d86f6a-68d1-40a1-87ed-2249606fb538"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_39"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mamangu ananiimbia wimbo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MSTARI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946791178682","data":{"timestamp":" 946791178682"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_083053"," gameId":" 22d86f6a-68d1-40a1-87ed-2249606fb538"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_39"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mamangu ananiimbia wimbo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HAPA"," userResponse":" HAPA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946791179908","data":{"timestamp":" 946791179908"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_083053"," gameId":" 22d86f6a-68d1-40a1-87ed-2249606fb538"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_39"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mamangu ananiimbia wimbo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NIMESIMAMA"," userResponse":" NIMESIMAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946791180351","data":{"timestamp":" 946791180351"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_083053"," gameId":" 22d86f6a-68d1-40a1-87ed-2249606fb538"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_39"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mamangu ananiimbia wimbo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWENYE"," userResponse":" KWENYE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946791181117","data":{"timestamp":" 946791181116"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_083053"," gameId":" 22d86f6a-68d1-40a1-87ed-2249606fb538"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_39"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mamangu ananiimbia wimbo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MSTARI"," userResponse":" MSTARI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946791183823","data":{"timestamp":" 946791183823"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_083053"," gameId":" 22d86f6a-68d1-40a1-87ed-2249606fb538"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_39"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mamangu ananiimbia wimbo."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAMANGU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946791186125","data":{"timestamp":" 946791186125"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_083053"," gameId":" 22d86f6a-68d1-40a1-87ed-2249606fb538"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_39"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mamangu ananiimbia wimbo."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANANIIMBIA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946791187963","data":{"timestamp":" 946791187962"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_083053"," gameId":" 22d86f6a-68d1-40a1-87ed-2249606fb538"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_39"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mamangu ananiimbia wimbo."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WIMBO"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946791189844","data":{"timestamp":" 946791189844"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_083053"," gameId":" 22d86f6a-68d1-40a1-87ed-2249606fb538"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_39"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mamangu ananiimbia wimbo."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAMANGU"," userResponse":" MAMANGU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946791191304","data":{"timestamp":" 946791191303"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_083053"," gameId":" 22d86f6a-68d1-40a1-87ed-2249606fb538"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_39"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mamangu ananiimbia wimbo."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANANIIMBIA"," userResponse":" ANANIIMBIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946791191757","data":{"timestamp":" 946791191757"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_083053"," gameId":" 22d86f6a-68d1-40a1-87ed-2249606fb538"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_39"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mamangu ananiimbia wimbo."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WIMBO"," userResponse":" WIMBO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946791194565","data":{"timestamp":" 946791194565"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_083053"," gameId":" 22d86f6a-68d1-40a1-87ed-2249606fb538"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_39"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Twasubiri Nanu na mimi!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NJOO"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946791196401","data":{"timestamp":" 946791196400"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_083053"," gameId":" 22d86f6a-68d1-40a1-87ed-2249606fb538"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_39"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Twasubiri Nanu na mimi!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BWANA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946791198007","data":{"timestamp":" 946791198007"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_083053"," gameId":" 22d86f6a-68d1-40a1-87ed-2249606fb538"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_39"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Twasubiri Nanu na mimi!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TEKSI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946791199845","data":{"timestamp":" 946791199845"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_083053"," gameId":" 22d86f6a-68d1-40a1-87ed-2249606fb538"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_39"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Twasubiri Nanu na mimi!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWANI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946791202016","data":{"timestamp":" 946791202016"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_083053"," gameId":" 22d86f6a-68d1-40a1-87ed-2249606fb538"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_39"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Twasubiri Nanu na mimi!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HUONI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946791203766","data":{"timestamp":" 946791203765"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_083053"," gameId":" 22d86f6a-68d1-40a1-87ed-2249606fb538"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_39"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Twasubiri Nanu na mimi!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NJOO"," userResponse":" NJOO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946791204124","data":{"timestamp":" 946791204124"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_083053"," gameId":" 22d86f6a-68d1-40a1-87ed-2249606fb538"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_39"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Twasubiri Nanu na mimi!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BWANA"," userResponse":" BWANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946791205088","data":{"timestamp":" 946791205087"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_083053"," gameId":" 22d86f6a-68d1-40a1-87ed-2249606fb538"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_39"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Twasubiri Nanu na mimi!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TEKSI"," userResponse":" TEKSI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946791205581","data":{"timestamp":" 946791205580"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_083053"," gameId":" 22d86f6a-68d1-40a1-87ed-2249606fb538"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_39"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Twasubiri Nanu na mimi!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWANI"," userResponse":" KWANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946791206467","data":{"timestamp":" 946791206467"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_083053"," gameId":" 22d86f6a-68d1-40a1-87ed-2249606fb538"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_39"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Twasubiri Nanu na mimi!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HUONI"," userResponse":" HUONI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946791210086","data":{"timestamp":" 946791210086"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_083053"," gameId":" 22d86f6a-68d1-40a1-87ed-2249606fb538"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_39"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Twasubiri Nanu na mimi!"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TWASUBIRI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946791211954","data":{"timestamp":" 946791211954"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_083053"," gameId":" 22d86f6a-68d1-40a1-87ed-2249606fb538"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_39"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Twasubiri Nanu na mimi!"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NANU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946791213561","data":{"timestamp":" 946791213561"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_083053"," gameId":" 22d86f6a-68d1-40a1-87ed-2249606fb538"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_39"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Twasubiri Nanu na mimi!"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946791215576","data":{"timestamp":" 946791215576"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_083053"," gameId":" 22d86f6a-68d1-40a1-87ed-2249606fb538"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_39"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Twasubiri Nanu na mimi!"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MIMI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946791217497","data":{"timestamp":" 946791217497"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_083053"," gameId":" 22d86f6a-68d1-40a1-87ed-2249606fb538"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_39"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Twasubiri Nanu na mimi!"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TWASUBIRI"," userResponse":" TWASUBIRI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946791218361","data":{"timestamp":" 946791218361"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_083053"," gameId":" 22d86f6a-68d1-40a1-87ed-2249606fb538"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_39"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Twasubiri Nanu na mimi!"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NANU"," userResponse":" NANU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946791219027","data":{"timestamp":" 946791219027"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_083053"," gameId":" 22d86f6a-68d1-40a1-87ed-2249606fb538"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_39"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Twasubiri Nanu na mimi!"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946791220112","data":{"timestamp":" 946791220111"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_083053"," gameId":" 22d86f6a-68d1-40a1-87ed-2249606fb538"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_39"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Twasubiri Nanu na mimi!"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MIMI"," userResponse":" MIMI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946791223054","data":{"timestamp":" 946791223053"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_083053"," gameId":" 22d86f6a-68d1-40a1-87ed-2249606fb538"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_39"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwanamke aliye karibu nami anawapeleka kuku nyumbani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MWANAMKE"," userResponse":" NAMI"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946791225437","data":{"timestamp":" 946791225437"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_083053"," gameId":" 22d86f6a-68d1-40a1-87ed-2249606fb538"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_39"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwanamke aliye karibu nami anawapeleka kuku nyumbani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MWANAMKE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946791227473","data":{"timestamp":" 946791227473"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_083053"," gameId":" 22d86f6a-68d1-40a1-87ed-2249606fb538"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_39"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwanamke aliye karibu nami anawapeleka kuku nyumbani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIYE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946791229462","data":{"timestamp":" 946791229462"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_083053"," gameId":" 22d86f6a-68d1-40a1-87ed-2249606fb538"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_39"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwanamke aliye karibu nami anawapeleka kuku nyumbani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KARIBU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946791231339","data":{"timestamp":" 946791231339"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_083053"," gameId":" 22d86f6a-68d1-40a1-87ed-2249606fb538"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_39"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwanamke aliye karibu nami anawapeleka kuku nyumbani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NAMI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946791234615","data":{"timestamp":" 946791234614"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_083053"," gameId":" 22d86f6a-68d1-40a1-87ed-2249606fb538"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_39"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwanamke aliye karibu nami anawapeleka kuku nyumbani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANAWAPELEKA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946791236273","data":{"timestamp":" 946791236273"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_083053"," gameId":" 22d86f6a-68d1-40a1-87ed-2249606fb538"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_39"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwanamke aliye karibu nami anawapeleka kuku nyumbani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUKU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946791238168","data":{"timestamp":" 946791238168"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_083053"," gameId":" 22d86f6a-68d1-40a1-87ed-2249606fb538"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_39"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwanamke aliye karibu nami anawapeleka kuku nyumbani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYUMBANI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946791240255","data":{"timestamp":" 946791240255"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_083053"," gameId":" 22d86f6a-68d1-40a1-87ed-2249606fb538"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_39"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwanamke aliye karibu nami anawapeleka kuku nyumbani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MWANAMKE"," userResponse":" MWANAMKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946791240738","data":{"timestamp":" 946791240738"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_083053"," gameId":" 22d86f6a-68d1-40a1-87ed-2249606fb538"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_39"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwanamke aliye karibu nami anawapeleka kuku nyumbani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIYE"," userResponse":" ALIYE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946791241356","data":{"timestamp":" 946791241355"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_083053"," gameId":" 22d86f6a-68d1-40a1-87ed-2249606fb538"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_39"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwanamke aliye karibu nami anawapeleka kuku nyumbani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KARIBU"," userResponse":" KARIBU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946791241934","data":{"timestamp":" 946791241934"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_083053"," gameId":" 22d86f6a-68d1-40a1-87ed-2249606fb538"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_39"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwanamke aliye karibu nami anawapeleka kuku nyumbani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NAMI"," userResponse":" NAMI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946791243262","data":{"timestamp":" 946791243261"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_083053"," gameId":" 22d86f6a-68d1-40a1-87ed-2249606fb538"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_39"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwanamke aliye karibu nami anawapeleka kuku nyumbani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANAWAPELEKA"," userResponse":" ANAWAPELEKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946791243658","data":{"timestamp":" 946791243657"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_083053"," gameId":" 22d86f6a-68d1-40a1-87ed-2249606fb538"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_39"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwanamke aliye karibu nami anawapeleka kuku nyumbani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUKU"," userResponse":" KUKU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946791244365","data":{"timestamp":" 946791244364"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_083053"," gameId":" 22d86f6a-68d1-40a1-87ed-2249606fb538"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_39"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwanamke aliye karibu nami anawapeleka kuku nyumbani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYUMBANI"," userResponse":" NYUMBANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946791246335","data":{"timestamp":" 946791246335"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_083053"," gameId":" 22d86f6a-68d1-40a1-87ed-2249606fb538"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_39"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watataga mayai ili ale."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" WATATAGA"," userResponse":" ALE"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946791247113","data":{"timestamp":" 946791247113"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_083053"," gameId":" 22d86f6a-68d1-40a1-87ed-2249606fb538"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_39"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watataga mayai ili ale."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" WATATAGA"," userResponse":" START_WATATAGA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946791248729","data":{"timestamp":" 946791248729"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_083053"," gameId":" 22d86f6a-68d1-40a1-87ed-2249606fb538"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_39"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watataga mayai ili ale."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WATATAGA"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946791251654","data":{"timestamp":" 946791251654"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_083053"," gameId":" 22d86f6a-68d1-40a1-87ed-2249606fb538"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_39"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watataga mayai ili ale."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAYAI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946791253740","data":{"timestamp":" 946791253740"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_083053"," gameId":" 22d86f6a-68d1-40a1-87ed-2249606fb538"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_39"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watataga mayai ili ale."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ILI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946791255529","data":{"timestamp":" 946791255528"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_083053"," gameId":" 22d86f6a-68d1-40a1-87ed-2249606fb538"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_39"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watataga mayai ili ale."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946791257547","data":{"timestamp":" 946791257547"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_083053"," gameId":" 22d86f6a-68d1-40a1-87ed-2249606fb538"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_39"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watataga mayai ili ale."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WATATAGA"," userResponse":" WATATAGA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946791258343","data":{"timestamp":" 946791258343"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_083053"," gameId":" 22d86f6a-68d1-40a1-87ed-2249606fb538"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_39"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watataga mayai ili ale."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAYAI"," userResponse":" MAYAI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946791258969","data":{"timestamp":" 946791258968"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_083053"," gameId":" 22d86f6a-68d1-40a1-87ed-2249606fb538"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_39"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watataga mayai ili ale."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ILI"," userResponse":" ILI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946791259320","data":{"timestamp":" 946791259320"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_083053"," gameId":" 22d86f6a-68d1-40a1-87ed-2249606fb538"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_39"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watataga mayai ili ale."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALE"," userResponse":" ALE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946791262951","data":{"timestamp":" 946791262951"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_083053"," gameId":" 22d86f6a-68d1-40a1-87ed-2249606fb538"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_39"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Teksi yaja kwa haraka."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WANAUME"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946791264952","data":{"timestamp":" 946791264952"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_083053"," gameId":" 22d86f6a-68d1-40a1-87ed-2249606fb538"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_39"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Teksi yaja kwa haraka."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HAWA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946791266860","data":{"timestamp":" 946791266860"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_083053"," gameId":" 22d86f6a-68d1-40a1-87ed-2249606fb538"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_39"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Teksi yaja kwa haraka."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WANARUDI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946791268580","data":{"timestamp":" 946791268580"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_083053"," gameId":" 22d86f6a-68d1-40a1-87ed-2249606fb538"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_39"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Teksi yaja kwa haraka."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUTOKA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946791270679","data":{"timestamp":" 946791270679"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_083053"," gameId":" 22d86f6a-68d1-40a1-87ed-2249606fb538"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_39"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Teksi yaja kwa haraka."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KAZI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946791272648","data":{"timestamp":" 946791272648"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_083053"," gameId":" 22d86f6a-68d1-40a1-87ed-2249606fb538"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_39"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Teksi yaja kwa haraka."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WANAUME"," userResponse":" WANAUME"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946791273341","data":{"timestamp":" 946791273340"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_083053"," gameId":" 22d86f6a-68d1-40a1-87ed-2249606fb538"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_39"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Teksi yaja kwa haraka."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HAWA"," userResponse":" HAWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946791274465","data":{"timestamp":" 946791274464"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_083053"," gameId":" 22d86f6a-68d1-40a1-87ed-2249606fb538"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_39"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Teksi yaja kwa haraka."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WANARUDI"," userResponse":" WANARUDI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946791275232","data":{"timestamp":" 946791275231"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_083053"," gameId":" 22d86f6a-68d1-40a1-87ed-2249606fb538"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_39"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Teksi yaja kwa haraka."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUTOKA"," userResponse":" KUTOKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946791275777","data":{"timestamp":" 946791275777"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_083053"," gameId":" 22d86f6a-68d1-40a1-87ed-2249606fb538"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_39"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Teksi yaja kwa haraka."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KAZI"," userResponse":" KAZI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946791278918","data":{"timestamp":" 946791278918"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_083053"," gameId":" 22d86f6a-68d1-40a1-87ed-2249606fb538"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_39"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Teksi yaja kwa haraka."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WANATABASAMU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946791281747","data":{"timestamp":" 946791281747"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_083053"," gameId":" 22d86f6a-68d1-40a1-87ed-2249606fb538"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_39"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Teksi yaja kwa haraka."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WANATABASAMU"," userResponse":" WANATABASAMU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946791284947","data":{"timestamp":" 946791284947"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_083053"," gameId":" 22d86f6a-68d1-40a1-87ed-2249606fb538"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_39"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Teksi yaja kwa haraka."," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NAWASIKIA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946791286934","data":{"timestamp":" 946791286934"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_083053"," gameId":" 22d86f6a-68d1-40a1-87ed-2249606fb538"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_39"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Teksi yaja kwa haraka."," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAKIIMBA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946791288798","data":{"timestamp":" 946791288798"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_083053"," gameId":" 22d86f6a-68d1-40a1-87ed-2249606fb538"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_39"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Teksi yaja kwa haraka."," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NANU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946791290834","data":{"timestamp":" 946791290834"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_083053"," gameId":" 22d86f6a-68d1-40a1-87ed-2249606fb538"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_39"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Teksi yaja kwa haraka."," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MDOGO"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946791292930","data":{"timestamp":" 946791292930"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_083053"," gameId":" 22d86f6a-68d1-40a1-87ed-2249606fb538"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_39"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Teksi yaja kwa haraka."," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" USIWE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946791294542","data":{"timestamp":" 946791294542"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_083053"," gameId":" 22d86f6a-68d1-40a1-87ed-2249606fb538"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_39"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Teksi yaja kwa haraka."," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946791296631","data":{"timestamp":" 946791296630"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_083053"," gameId":" 22d86f6a-68d1-40a1-87ed-2249606fb538"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_39"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Teksi yaja kwa haraka."," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WASIWASI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946791298714","data":{"timestamp":" 946791298714"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_083053"," gameId":" 22d86f6a-68d1-40a1-87ed-2249606fb538"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_39"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Teksi yaja kwa haraka."," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NAWASIKIA"," userResponse":" NAWASIKIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946791299500","data":{"timestamp":" 946791299500"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_083053"," gameId":" 22d86f6a-68d1-40a1-87ed-2249606fb538"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_39"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Teksi yaja kwa haraka."," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAKIIMBA"," userResponse":" WAKIIMBA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946791300427","data":{"timestamp":" 946791300426"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_083053"," gameId":" 22d86f6a-68d1-40a1-87ed-2249606fb538"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_39"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Teksi yaja kwa haraka."," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NANU"," userResponse":" NANU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946791301244","data":{"timestamp":" 946791301243"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_083053"," gameId":" 22d86f6a-68d1-40a1-87ed-2249606fb538"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_39"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Teksi yaja kwa haraka."," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MDOGO"," userResponse":" MDOGO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946791301749","data":{"timestamp":" 946791301748"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_083053"," gameId":" 22d86f6a-68d1-40a1-87ed-2249606fb538"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_39"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Teksi yaja kwa haraka."," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" USIWE"," userResponse":" USIWE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946791302043","data":{"timestamp":" 946791302042"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_083053"," gameId":" 22d86f6a-68d1-40a1-87ed-2249606fb538"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_39"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Teksi yaja kwa haraka."," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946791303190","data":{"timestamp":" 946791303189"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_083053"," gameId":" 22d86f6a-68d1-40a1-87ed-2249606fb538"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_39"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Teksi yaja kwa haraka."," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WASIWASI"," userResponse":" WASIWASI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946791306040","data":{"timestamp":" 946791306039"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_083053"," gameId":" 22d86f6a-68d1-40a1-87ed-2249606fb538"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_39"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Teksi yaja kwa haraka."," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TEKSI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946791307853","data":{"timestamp":" 946791307853"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_083053"," gameId":" 22d86f6a-68d1-40a1-87ed-2249606fb538"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_39"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Teksi yaja kwa haraka."," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YAJA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946791309331","data":{"timestamp":" 946791309331"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_083053"," gameId":" 22d86f6a-68d1-40a1-87ed-2249606fb538"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_39"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Teksi yaja kwa haraka."," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946791311541","data":{"timestamp":" 946791311540"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_083053"," gameId":" 22d86f6a-68d1-40a1-87ed-2249606fb538"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_39"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Teksi yaja kwa haraka."," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HARAKA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946791313473","data":{"timestamp":" 946791313472"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_083053"," gameId":" 22d86f6a-68d1-40a1-87ed-2249606fb538"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_39"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Teksi yaja kwa haraka."," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TEKSI"," userResponse":" TEKSI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946791313804","data":{"timestamp":" 946791313804"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_083053"," gameId":" 22d86f6a-68d1-40a1-87ed-2249606fb538"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_39"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Teksi yaja kwa haraka."," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YAJA"," userResponse":" YAJA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946791314069","data":{"timestamp":" 946791314069"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_083053"," gameId":" 22d86f6a-68d1-40a1-87ed-2249606fb538"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_39"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Teksi yaja kwa haraka."," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946791315064","data":{"timestamp":" 946791315063"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_083053"," gameId":" 22d86f6a-68d1-40a1-87ed-2249606fb538"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_39"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Teksi yaja kwa haraka."," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HARAKA"," userResponse":" HARAKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946791319559","data":{"timestamp":" 946791319559"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_083053"," gameId":" 22d86f6a-68d1-40a1-87ed-2249606fb538"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_39"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Je unavipenda?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MWANAMME"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946791321800","data":{"timestamp":" 946791321800"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_083053"," gameId":" 22d86f6a-68d1-40a1-87ed-2249606fb538"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_39"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Je unavipenda?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HUYO"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946791324865","data":{"timestamp":" 946791324865"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_083053"," gameId":" 22d86f6a-68d1-40a1-87ed-2249606fb538"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_39"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Je unavipenda?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANAUZA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946791326934","data":{"timestamp":" 946791326934"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_083053"," gameId":" 22d86f6a-68d1-40a1-87ed-2249606fb538"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_39"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Je unavipenda?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VINYWAJI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946791329118","data":{"timestamp":" 946791329118"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_083053"," gameId":" 22d86f6a-68d1-40a1-87ed-2249606fb538"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_39"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Je unavipenda?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BARIDI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946791331142","data":{"timestamp":" 946791331142"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_083053"," gameId":" 22d86f6a-68d1-40a1-87ed-2249606fb538"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_39"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Je unavipenda?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MWANAMME"," userResponse":" MWANAMME"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946791331765","data":{"timestamp":" 946791331765"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_083053"," gameId":" 22d86f6a-68d1-40a1-87ed-2249606fb538"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_39"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Je unavipenda?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HUYO"," userResponse":" HUYO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946791331790","data":{"timestamp":" 946791331790"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_083053"," gameId":" 22d86f6a-68d1-40a1-87ed-2249606fb538"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_39"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Je unavipenda?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946791331876","data":{"timestamp":" 946791331876"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_083053"," gameId":" 22d86f6a-68d1-40a1-87ed-2249606fb538"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_39"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Je unavipenda?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HUYO"," userResponse":" HUYO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"num.scale:72..82.off1.11__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946791370054","data":{"timestamp":" 946791370054"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_083053"," gameId":" 22d86f6a-68d1-40a1-87ed-2249606fb538"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_39"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" Je unavipenda?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946791384656","data":{"timestamp":" 946791384655"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_083053"," gameId":" 4289905c-c158-4ca6-a764-99ae267c0740"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_mkulima"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" m"," userResponse":" m"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946791385409","data":{"timestamp":" 946791385409"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_083053"," gameId":" 4289905c-c158-4ca6-a764-99ae267c0740"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_mkulima"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ku"," userResponse":" ku"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946791387075","data":{"timestamp":" 946791387075"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_083053"," gameId":" 4289905c-c158-4ca6-a764-99ae267c0740"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_mkulima"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" li"," userResponse":" li"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946791387574","data":{"timestamp":" 946791387574"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_083053"," gameId":" 4289905c-c158-4ca6-a764-99ae267c0740"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_mkulima"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ma"," userResponse":" ma"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946791396786","data":{"timestamp":" 946791396785"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_083053"," gameId":" 4289905c-c158-4ca6-a764-99ae267c0740"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_tikitimaji"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ti"," userResponse":" ti"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946791397429","data":{"timestamp":" 946791397429"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_083053"," gameId":" 4289905c-c158-4ca6-a764-99ae267c0740"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_tikitimaji"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ki"," userResponse":" ki"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946791399807","data":{"timestamp":" 946791399807"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_083053"," gameId":" 4289905c-c158-4ca6-a764-99ae267c0740"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_tikitimaji"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ti"," userResponse":" ti"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946791401486","data":{"timestamp":" 946791401486"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_083053"," gameId":" 4289905c-c158-4ca6-a764-99ae267c0740"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_tikitimaji"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ma"," userResponse":" ma"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946791402157","data":{"timestamp":" 946791402157"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_083053"," gameId":" 4289905c-c158-4ca6-a764-99ae267c0740"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_tikitimaji"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ji"," userResponse":" ji"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946791406293","data":{"timestamp":" 946791406293"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_083053"," gameId":" 4289905c-c158-4ca6-a764-99ae267c0740"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_kitunguu"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ki"," userResponse":" ki"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946791407592","data":{"timestamp":" 946791407591"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_083053"," gameId":" 4289905c-c158-4ca6-a764-99ae267c0740"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_kitunguu"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" tu"," userResponse":" tu"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946791408729","data":{"timestamp":" 946791408729"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_083053"," gameId":" 4289905c-c158-4ca6-a764-99ae267c0740"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_kitunguu"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ngu"," userResponse":" ngu"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946791409355","data":{"timestamp":" 946791409355"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_083053"," gameId":" 4289905c-c158-4ca6-a764-99ae267c0740"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_kitunguu"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" u"," userResponse":" u"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946791414841","data":{"timestamp":" 946791414841"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_083053"," gameId":" 4289905c-c158-4ca6-a764-99ae267c0740"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_wanawake"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" wa"," userResponse":" wa"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946791416310","data":{"timestamp":" 946791416310"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_083053"," gameId":" 4289905c-c158-4ca6-a764-99ae267c0740"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_wanawake"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" na"," userResponse":" na"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946791418024","data":{"timestamp":" 946791418024"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_083053"," gameId":" 4289905c-c158-4ca6-a764-99ae267c0740"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_wanawake"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" wa"," userResponse":" wa"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946791418855","data":{"timestamp":" 946791418855"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_083053"," gameId":" 4289905c-c158-4ca6-a764-99ae267c0740"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_wanawake"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ke"," userResponse":" ke"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946791423178","data":{"timestamp":" 946791423178"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_083053"," gameId":" 4289905c-c158-4ca6-a764-99ae267c0740"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_tabasamu"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ta"," userResponse":" ta"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946791424375","data":{"timestamp":" 946791424375"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_083053"," gameId":" 4289905c-c158-4ca6-a764-99ae267c0740"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_tabasamu"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ba"," userResponse":" ba"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946791425750","data":{"timestamp":" 946791425750"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_083053"," gameId":" 4289905c-c158-4ca6-a764-99ae267c0740"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_tabasamu"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" sa"," userResponse":" sa"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946791426368","data":{"timestamp":" 946791426368"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_083053"," gameId":" 4289905c-c158-4ca6-a764-99ae267c0740"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_tabasamu"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" mu"," userResponse":" mu"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946791431014","data":{"timestamp":" 946791431014"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_083053"," gameId":" 4289905c-c158-4ca6-a764-99ae267c0740"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_anaoga"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" a"," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946791432720","data":{"timestamp":" 946791432720"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_083053"," gameId":" 4289905c-c158-4ca6-a764-99ae267c0740"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_anaoga"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" na"," userResponse":" na"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946791434656","data":{"timestamp":" 946791434656"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_083053"," gameId":" 4289905c-c158-4ca6-a764-99ae267c0740"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_anaoga"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" o"," userResponse":" o"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946791435239","data":{"timestamp":" 946791435239"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_083053"," gameId":" 4289905c-c158-4ca6-a764-99ae267c0740"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_anaoga"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ga"," userResponse":" ga"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946791440046","data":{"timestamp":" 946791440046"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_083053"," gameId":" 4289905c-c158-4ca6-a764-99ae267c0740"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_pundamilia"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" pu"," userResponse":" pu"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946791443171","data":{"timestamp":" 946791443170"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_083053"," gameId":" 4289905c-c158-4ca6-a764-99ae267c0740"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_pundamilia"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" nda"," userResponse":" nda"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946791445192","data":{"timestamp":" 946791445191"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_083053"," gameId":" 4289905c-c158-4ca6-a764-99ae267c0740"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_pundamilia"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" mi"," userResponse":" mi"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946791446711","data":{"timestamp":" 946791446710"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_083053"," gameId":" 4289905c-c158-4ca6-a764-99ae267c0740"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_pundamilia"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" li"," userResponse":" li"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946791447031","data":{"timestamp":" 946791447031"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_083053"," gameId":" 4289905c-c158-4ca6-a764-99ae267c0740"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_pundamilia"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" a"," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946791452620","data":{"timestamp":" 946791452620"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_083053"," gameId":" 4289905c-c158-4ca6-a764-99ae267c0740"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_alicheza"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" a"," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946791453093","data":{"timestamp":" 946791453093"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_083053"," gameId":" 4289905c-c158-4ca6-a764-99ae267c0740"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_alicheza"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" li"," userResponse":" che"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946791459368","data":{"timestamp":" 946791459368"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_083053"," gameId":" 4289905c-c158-4ca6-a764-99ae267c0740"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_alicheza"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" li"," userResponse":" li"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946791459782","data":{"timestamp":" 946791459782"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_083053"," gameId":" 4289905c-c158-4ca6-a764-99ae267c0740"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_alicheza"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" che"," userResponse":" che"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946791460199","data":{"timestamp":" 946791460198"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_083053"," gameId":" 4289905c-c158-4ca6-a764-99ae267c0740"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_alicheza"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" za"," userResponse":" za"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946791466975","data":{"timestamp":" 946791466975"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_083053"," gameId":" 4289905c-c158-4ca6-a764-99ae267c0740"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_wakiruka"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" wa"," userResponse":" wa"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946791467882","data":{"timestamp":" 946791467881"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_083053"," gameId":" 4289905c-c158-4ca6-a764-99ae267c0740"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_wakiruka"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ki"," userResponse":" ki"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946791468450","data":{"timestamp":" 946791468450"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_083053"," gameId":" 4289905c-c158-4ca6-a764-99ae267c0740"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_wakiruka"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ru"," userResponse":" ru"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946791468968","data":{"timestamp":" 946791468968"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_083053"," gameId":" 4289905c-c158-4ca6-a764-99ae267c0740"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_wakiruka"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ka"," userResponse":" ka"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946791473538","data":{"timestamp":" 946791473538"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_083053"," gameId":" 4289905c-c158-4ca6-a764-99ae267c0740"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_mpapai"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" m"," userResponse":" m"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946791474529","data":{"timestamp":" 946791474529"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_083053"," gameId":" 4289905c-c158-4ca6-a764-99ae267c0740"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_mpapai"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" pa"," userResponse":" pa"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946791474877","data":{"timestamp":" 946791474877"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_083053"," gameId":" 4289905c-c158-4ca6-a764-99ae267c0740"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_mpapai"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" pa"," userResponse":" pa"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946791476229","data":{"timestamp":" 946791476229"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_083053"," gameId":" 4289905c-c158-4ca6-a764-99ae267c0740"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_mpapai"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" i"," userResponse":" i"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946791479301","data":{"timestamp":" 946791479301"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_083053"," gameId":" 4289905c-c158-4ca6-a764-99ae267c0740"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" write_mpapai"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946791484996","data":{"timestamp":" 946791484996"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_083053"," gameId":" 4289905c-c158-4ca6-a764-99ae267c0740"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" write_mpapai"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946791505483","data":{"timestamp":" 946791505482"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_083053"," gameId":" 18bf14a0-8260-4c05-bdde-ffdcb6f26518"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watu wa kijiji cha vyumba vidogo walikuwa wanaanza kutokuwa na furaha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WATU"," userResponse":" WATU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946791505736","data":{"timestamp":" 946791505735"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_083053"," gameId":" 18bf14a0-8260-4c05-bdde-ffdcb6f26518"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watu wa kijiji cha vyumba vidogo walikuwa wanaanza kutokuwa na furaha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WA"," userResponse":" WA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946791506632","data":{"timestamp":" 946791506631"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_083053"," gameId":" 18bf14a0-8260-4c05-bdde-ffdcb6f26518"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watu wa kijiji cha vyumba vidogo walikuwa wanaanza kutokuwa na furaha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIJIJI"," userResponse":" KIJIJI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946791507139","data":{"timestamp":" 946791507138"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_083053"," gameId":" 18bf14a0-8260-4c05-bdde-ffdcb6f26518"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watu wa kijiji cha vyumba vidogo walikuwa wanaanza kutokuwa na furaha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHA"," userResponse":" CHA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946791507723","data":{"timestamp":" 946791507723"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_083053"," gameId":" 18bf14a0-8260-4c05-bdde-ffdcb6f26518"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watu wa kijiji cha vyumba vidogo walikuwa wanaanza kutokuwa na furaha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VYUMBA"," userResponse":" VYUMBA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946791508649","data":{"timestamp":" 946791508648"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_083053"," gameId":" 18bf14a0-8260-4c05-bdde-ffdcb6f26518"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watu wa kijiji cha vyumba vidogo walikuwa wanaanza kutokuwa na furaha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VIDOGO"," userResponse":" VIDOGO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946791509788","data":{"timestamp":" 946791509788"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_083053"," gameId":" 18bf14a0-8260-4c05-bdde-ffdcb6f26518"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watu wa kijiji cha vyumba vidogo walikuwa wanaanza kutokuwa na furaha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALIKUWA"," userResponse":" WALIKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946791510672","data":{"timestamp":" 946791510671"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_083053"," gameId":" 18bf14a0-8260-4c05-bdde-ffdcb6f26518"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watu wa kijiji cha vyumba vidogo walikuwa wanaanza kutokuwa na furaha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WANAANZA"," userResponse":" WANAANZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946791511486","data":{"timestamp":" 946791511486"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_083053"," gameId":" 18bf14a0-8260-4c05-bdde-ffdcb6f26518"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watu wa kijiji cha vyumba vidogo walikuwa wanaanza kutokuwa na furaha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUTOKUWA"," userResponse":" KUTOKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946791511768","data":{"timestamp":" 946791511768"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_083053"," gameId":" 18bf14a0-8260-4c05-bdde-ffdcb6f26518"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watu wa kijiji cha vyumba vidogo walikuwa wanaanza kutokuwa na furaha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946791512564","data":{"timestamp":" 946791512563"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_083053"," gameId":" 18bf14a0-8260-4c05-bdde-ffdcb6f26518"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watu wa kijiji cha vyumba vidogo walikuwa wanaanza kutokuwa na furaha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" FURAHA"," userResponse":" FURAHA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946791514937","data":{"timestamp":" 946791514937"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_083053"," gameId":" 18bf14a0-8260-4c05-bdde-ffdcb6f26518"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watu wa kijiji cha vyumba vidogo walikuwa wanaanza kutokuwa na furaha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WATU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946791516562","data":{"timestamp":" 946791516562"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_083053"," gameId":" 18bf14a0-8260-4c05-bdde-ffdcb6f26518"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watu wa kijiji cha vyumba vidogo walikuwa wanaanza kutokuwa na furaha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946791518698","data":{"timestamp":" 946791518698"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_083053"," gameId":" 18bf14a0-8260-4c05-bdde-ffdcb6f26518"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watu wa kijiji cha vyumba vidogo walikuwa wanaanza kutokuwa na furaha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIJIJI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946791520448","data":{"timestamp":" 946791520448"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_083053"," gameId":" 18bf14a0-8260-4c05-bdde-ffdcb6f26518"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watu wa kijiji cha vyumba vidogo walikuwa wanaanza kutokuwa na furaha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946791522630","data":{"timestamp":" 946791522630"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_083053"," gameId":" 18bf14a0-8260-4c05-bdde-ffdcb6f26518"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watu wa kijiji cha vyumba vidogo walikuwa wanaanza kutokuwa na furaha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VYUMBA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946791524782","data":{"timestamp":" 946791524782"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_083053"," gameId":" 18bf14a0-8260-4c05-bdde-ffdcb6f26518"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watu wa kijiji cha vyumba vidogo walikuwa wanaanza kutokuwa na furaha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VIDOGO"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946791527057","data":{"timestamp":" 946791527057"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_083053"," gameId":" 18bf14a0-8260-4c05-bdde-ffdcb6f26518"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watu wa kijiji cha vyumba vidogo walikuwa wanaanza kutokuwa na furaha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALIKUWA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946791529075","data":{"timestamp":" 946791529074"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_083053"," gameId":" 18bf14a0-8260-4c05-bdde-ffdcb6f26518"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watu wa kijiji cha vyumba vidogo walikuwa wanaanza kutokuwa na furaha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WANAANZA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946791530865","data":{"timestamp":" 946791530865"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_083053"," gameId":" 18bf14a0-8260-4c05-bdde-ffdcb6f26518"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watu wa kijiji cha vyumba vidogo walikuwa wanaanza kutokuwa na furaha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUTOKUWA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946791532586","data":{"timestamp":" 946791532586"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_083053"," gameId":" 18bf14a0-8260-4c05-bdde-ffdcb6f26518"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watu wa kijiji cha vyumba vidogo walikuwa wanaanza kutokuwa na furaha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946791534564","data":{"timestamp":" 946791534564"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_083053"," gameId":" 18bf14a0-8260-4c05-bdde-ffdcb6f26518"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watu wa kijiji cha vyumba vidogo walikuwa wanaanza kutokuwa na furaha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" FURAHA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946791536527","data":{"timestamp":" 946791536527"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_083053"," gameId":" 18bf14a0-8260-4c05-bdde-ffdcb6f26518"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wanyama wa mwituni walianza kufika pale na kuwaogofya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WANYAMA"," userResponse":" WANYAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946791536729","data":{"timestamp":" 946791536729"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_083053"," gameId":" 18bf14a0-8260-4c05-bdde-ffdcb6f26518"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wanyama wa mwituni walianza kufika pale na kuwaogofya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WA"," userResponse":" WA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946791537577","data":{"timestamp":" 946791537576"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_083053"," gameId":" 18bf14a0-8260-4c05-bdde-ffdcb6f26518"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wanyama wa mwituni walianza kufika pale na kuwaogofya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MWITUNI"," userResponse":" MWITUNI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946791538411","data":{"timestamp":" 946791538411"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_083053"," gameId":" 18bf14a0-8260-4c05-bdde-ffdcb6f26518"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wanyama wa mwituni walianza kufika pale na kuwaogofya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALIANZA"," userResponse":" WALIANZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946791539077","data":{"timestamp":" 946791539077"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_083053"," gameId":" 18bf14a0-8260-4c05-bdde-ffdcb6f26518"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wanyama wa mwituni walianza kufika pale na kuwaogofya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUFIKA"," userResponse":" KUFIKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946791539702","data":{"timestamp":" 946791539702"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_083053"," gameId":" 18bf14a0-8260-4c05-bdde-ffdcb6f26518"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wanyama wa mwituni walianza kufika pale na kuwaogofya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PALE"," userResponse":" PALE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946791540275","data":{"timestamp":" 946791540274"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_083053"," gameId":" 18bf14a0-8260-4c05-bdde-ffdcb6f26518"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wanyama wa mwituni walianza kufika pale na kuwaogofya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946791541594","data":{"timestamp":" 946791541594"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_083053"," gameId":" 18bf14a0-8260-4c05-bdde-ffdcb6f26518"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wanyama wa mwituni walianza kufika pale na kuwaogofya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUWAOGOFYA"," userResponse":" KUWAOGOFYA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946791544490","data":{"timestamp":" 946791544490"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_083053"," gameId":" 18bf14a0-8260-4c05-bdde-ffdcb6f26518"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wanyama wa mwituni walianza kufika pale na kuwaogofya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WANYAMA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946791546108","data":{"timestamp":" 946791546108"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_083053"," gameId":" 18bf14a0-8260-4c05-bdde-ffdcb6f26518"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wanyama wa mwituni walianza kufika pale na kuwaogofya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946791548004","data":{"timestamp":" 946791548004"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_083053"," gameId":" 18bf14a0-8260-4c05-bdde-ffdcb6f26518"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wanyama wa mwituni walianza kufika pale na kuwaogofya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MWITUNI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946791549787","data":{"timestamp":" 946791549787"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_083053"," gameId":" 18bf14a0-8260-4c05-bdde-ffdcb6f26518"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wanyama wa mwituni walianza kufika pale na kuwaogofya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALIANZA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946791551579","data":{"timestamp":" 946791551579"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_083053"," gameId":" 18bf14a0-8260-4c05-bdde-ffdcb6f26518"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wanyama wa mwituni walianza kufika pale na kuwaogofya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUFIKA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946791553491","data":{"timestamp":" 946791553491"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_083053"," gameId":" 18bf14a0-8260-4c05-bdde-ffdcb6f26518"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wanyama wa mwituni walianza kufika pale na kuwaogofya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PALE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946791555218","data":{"timestamp":" 946791555218"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_083053"," gameId":" 18bf14a0-8260-4c05-bdde-ffdcb6f26518"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wanyama wa mwituni walianza kufika pale na kuwaogofya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946791557725","data":{"timestamp":" 946791557725"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_083053"," gameId":" 18bf14a0-8260-4c05-bdde-ffdcb6f26518"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wanyama wa mwituni walianza kufika pale na kuwaogofya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUWAOGOFYA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946791560144","data":{"timestamp":" 946791560143"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_083053"," gameId":" 18bf14a0-8260-4c05-bdde-ffdcb6f26518"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wanyama hawa walikula mimea yao yote."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WANYAMA"," userResponse":" WANYAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946791560618","data":{"timestamp":" 946791560618"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_083053"," gameId":" 18bf14a0-8260-4c05-bdde-ffdcb6f26518"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wanyama hawa walikula mimea yao yote."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HAWA"," userResponse":" HAWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946791561472","data":{"timestamp":" 946791561471"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_083053"," gameId":" 18bf14a0-8260-4c05-bdde-ffdcb6f26518"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wanyama hawa walikula mimea yao yote."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALIKULA"," userResponse":" WALIKULA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946791562135","data":{"timestamp":" 946791562135"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_083053"," gameId":" 18bf14a0-8260-4c05-bdde-ffdcb6f26518"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wanyama hawa walikula mimea yao yote."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MIMEA"," userResponse":" MIMEA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946791562678","data":{"timestamp":" 946791562678"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_083053"," gameId":" 18bf14a0-8260-4c05-bdde-ffdcb6f26518"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wanyama hawa walikula mimea yao yote."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YAO"," userResponse":" YAO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946791563254","data":{"timestamp":" 946791563254"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_083053"," gameId":" 18bf14a0-8260-4c05-bdde-ffdcb6f26518"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wanyama hawa walikula mimea yao yote."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YOTE"," userResponse":" YOTE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946791566101","data":{"timestamp":" 946791566101"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_083053"," gameId":" 18bf14a0-8260-4c05-bdde-ffdcb6f26518"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wanyama hawa walikula mimea yao yote."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WANYAMA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946791568616","data":{"timestamp":" 946791568616"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_083053"," gameId":" 18bf14a0-8260-4c05-bdde-ffdcb6f26518"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wanyama hawa walikula mimea yao yote."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HAWA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946791571601","data":{"timestamp":" 946791571601"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_083053"," gameId":" 18bf14a0-8260-4c05-bdde-ffdcb6f26518"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wanyama hawa walikula mimea yao yote."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALIKULA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946791574599","data":{"timestamp":" 946791574598"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_083053"," gameId":" 18bf14a0-8260-4c05-bdde-ffdcb6f26518"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wanyama hawa walikula mimea yao yote."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MIMEA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946791576845","data":{"timestamp":" 946791576845"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_083053"," gameId":" 18bf14a0-8260-4c05-bdde-ffdcb6f26518"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wanyama hawa walikula mimea yao yote."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YAO"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946791579858","data":{"timestamp":" 946791579858"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_083053"," gameId":" 18bf14a0-8260-4c05-bdde-ffdcb6f26518"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wanyama hawa walikula mimea yao yote."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YOTE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946791581612","data":{"timestamp":" 946791581611"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_083053"," gameId":" 18bf14a0-8260-4c05-bdde-ffdcb6f26518"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hata waliwabeba watoto na kuwaondosha pale."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HATA"," userResponse":" HATA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946791582805","data":{"timestamp":" 946791582805"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_083053"," gameId":" 18bf14a0-8260-4c05-bdde-ffdcb6f26518"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hata waliwabeba watoto na kuwaondosha pale."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALIWABEBA"," userResponse":" WALIWABEBA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946791583854","data":{"timestamp":" 946791583853"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_083053"," gameId":" 18bf14a0-8260-4c05-bdde-ffdcb6f26518"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hata waliwabeba watoto na kuwaondosha pale."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WATOTO"," userResponse":" WATOTO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946791584090","data":{"timestamp":" 946791584090"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_083053"," gameId":" 18bf14a0-8260-4c05-bdde-ffdcb6f26518"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hata waliwabeba watoto na kuwaondosha pale."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946791585218","data":{"timestamp":" 946791585217"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_083053"," gameId":" 18bf14a0-8260-4c05-bdde-ffdcb6f26518"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hata waliwabeba watoto na kuwaondosha pale."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUWAONDOSHA"," userResponse":" KUWAONDOSHA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946791585622","data":{"timestamp":" 946791585622"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_083053"," gameId":" 18bf14a0-8260-4c05-bdde-ffdcb6f26518"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hata waliwabeba watoto na kuwaondosha pale."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PALE"," userResponse":" PALE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946791588935","data":{"timestamp":" 946791588935"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_083053"," gameId":" 18bf14a0-8260-4c05-bdde-ffdcb6f26518"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hata waliwabeba watoto na kuwaondosha pale."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HATA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946791590907","data":{"timestamp":" 946791590907"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_083053"," gameId":" 18bf14a0-8260-4c05-bdde-ffdcb6f26518"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hata waliwabeba watoto na kuwaondosha pale."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALIWABEBA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946791592925","data":{"timestamp":" 946791592925"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_083053"," gameId":" 18bf14a0-8260-4c05-bdde-ffdcb6f26518"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hata waliwabeba watoto na kuwaondosha pale."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WATOTO"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946791594536","data":{"timestamp":" 946791594536"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_083053"," gameId":" 18bf14a0-8260-4c05-bdde-ffdcb6f26518"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hata waliwabeba watoto na kuwaondosha pale."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946791596660","data":{"timestamp":" 946791596660"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_083053"," gameId":" 18bf14a0-8260-4c05-bdde-ffdcb6f26518"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hata waliwabeba watoto na kuwaondosha pale."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUWAONDOSHA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946791599250","data":{"timestamp":" 946791599250"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_083053"," gameId":" 18bf14a0-8260-4c05-bdde-ffdcb6f26518"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hata waliwabeba watoto na kuwaondosha pale."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PALE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946791601608","data":{"timestamp":" 946791601608"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_083053"," gameId":" 18bf14a0-8260-4c05-bdde-ffdcb6f26518"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapakuwa pahali pazuri pa kuishi tena."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HAPAKUWA"," userResponse":" HAPAKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946791602294","data":{"timestamp":" 946791602294"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_083053"," gameId":" 18bf14a0-8260-4c05-bdde-ffdcb6f26518"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapakuwa pahali pazuri pa kuishi tena."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PAHALI"," userResponse":" PAHALI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946791603061","data":{"timestamp":" 946791603060"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_083053"," gameId":" 18bf14a0-8260-4c05-bdde-ffdcb6f26518"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapakuwa pahali pazuri pa kuishi tena."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PAZURI"," userResponse":" PAZURI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946791603274","data":{"timestamp":" 946791603274"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_083053"," gameId":" 18bf14a0-8260-4c05-bdde-ffdcb6f26518"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapakuwa pahali pazuri pa kuishi tena."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PA"," userResponse":" PA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946791603978","data":{"timestamp":" 946791603978"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_083053"," gameId":" 18bf14a0-8260-4c05-bdde-ffdcb6f26518"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapakuwa pahali pazuri pa kuishi tena."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUISHI"," userResponse":" KUISHI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946791604601","data":{"timestamp":" 946791604601"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_083053"," gameId":" 18bf14a0-8260-4c05-bdde-ffdcb6f26518"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapakuwa pahali pazuri pa kuishi tena."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TENA"," userResponse":" TENA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946791607950","data":{"timestamp":" 946791607950"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_083053"," gameId":" 18bf14a0-8260-4c05-bdde-ffdcb6f26518"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapakuwa pahali pazuri pa kuishi tena."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HAPAKUWA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946791610091","data":{"timestamp":" 946791610091"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_083053"," gameId":" 18bf14a0-8260-4c05-bdde-ffdcb6f26518"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapakuwa pahali pazuri pa kuishi tena."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PAHALI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946791612119","data":{"timestamp":" 946791612119"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_083053"," gameId":" 18bf14a0-8260-4c05-bdde-ffdcb6f26518"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapakuwa pahali pazuri pa kuishi tena."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PAZURI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946791613700","data":{"timestamp":" 946791613700"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_083053"," gameId":" 18bf14a0-8260-4c05-bdde-ffdcb6f26518"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapakuwa pahali pazuri pa kuishi tena."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946791615687","data":{"timestamp":" 946791615687"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_083053"," gameId":" 18bf14a0-8260-4c05-bdde-ffdcb6f26518"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapakuwa pahali pazuri pa kuishi tena."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUISHI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946791619500","data":{"timestamp":" 946791619500"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_083053"," gameId":" 18bf14a0-8260-4c05-bdde-ffdcb6f26518"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapakuwa pahali pazuri pa kuishi tena."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TENA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946791621415","data":{"timestamp":" 946791621415"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_083053"," gameId":" 18bf14a0-8260-4c05-bdde-ffdcb6f26518"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini wangeenda wapi?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LAKINI"," userResponse":" LAKINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946791622222","data":{"timestamp":" 946791622222"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_083053"," gameId":" 18bf14a0-8260-4c05-bdde-ffdcb6f26518"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini wangeenda wapi?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WANGEENDA"," userResponse":" WANGEENDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946791623155","data":{"timestamp":" 946791623154"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_083053"," gameId":" 18bf14a0-8260-4c05-bdde-ffdcb6f26518"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini wangeenda wapi?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAPI"," userResponse":" WAPI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946791626461","data":{"timestamp":" 946791626460"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_083053"," gameId":" 18bf14a0-8260-4c05-bdde-ffdcb6f26518"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini wangeenda wapi?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LAKINI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946791628358","data":{"timestamp":" 946791628358"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_083053"," gameId":" 18bf14a0-8260-4c05-bdde-ffdcb6f26518"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini wangeenda wapi?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WANGEENDA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946791630485","data":{"timestamp":" 946791630485"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_083053"," gameId":" 18bf14a0-8260-4c05-bdde-ffdcb6f26518"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini wangeenda wapi?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAPI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946791632962","data":{"timestamp":" 946791632961"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_083053"," gameId":" 18bf14a0-8260-4c05-bdde-ffdcb6f26518"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Familia moja ilipata jibu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" FAMILIA"," userResponse":" FAMILIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946791633544","data":{"timestamp":" 946791633544"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_083053"," gameId":" 18bf14a0-8260-4c05-bdde-ffdcb6f26518"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Familia moja ilipata jibu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MOJA"," userResponse":" MOJA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946791634489","data":{"timestamp":" 946791634488"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_083053"," gameId":" 18bf14a0-8260-4c05-bdde-ffdcb6f26518"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Familia moja ilipata jibu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ILIPATA"," userResponse":" ILIPATA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946791635082","data":{"timestamp":" 946791635081"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_083053"," gameId":" 18bf14a0-8260-4c05-bdde-ffdcb6f26518"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Familia moja ilipata jibu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JIBU"," userResponse":" JIBU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946791638388","data":{"timestamp":" 946791638388"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_083053"," gameId":" 18bf14a0-8260-4c05-bdde-ffdcb6f26518"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Familia moja ilipata jibu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" FAMILIA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946791639541","data":{"timestamp":" 946791639541"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_083053"," gameId":" 18bf14a0-8260-4c05-bdde-ffdcb6f26518"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Familia moja ilipata jibu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MOJA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946791641688","data":{"timestamp":" 946791641688"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_083053"," gameId":" 18bf14a0-8260-4c05-bdde-ffdcb6f26518"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Familia moja ilipata jibu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ILIPATA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946791643269","data":{"timestamp":" 946791643269"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_083053"," gameId":" 18bf14a0-8260-4c05-bdde-ffdcb6f26518"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Familia moja ilipata jibu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JIBU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946791645380","data":{"timestamp":" 946791645380"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_083053"," gameId":" 18bf14a0-8260-4c05-bdde-ffdcb6f26518"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Haikuwa vigumu kupata chakula milimani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HAIKUWA"," userResponse":" HAIKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946791646152","data":{"timestamp":" 946791646151"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_083053"," gameId":" 18bf14a0-8260-4c05-bdde-ffdcb6f26518"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Haikuwa vigumu kupata chakula milimani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VIGUMU"," userResponse":" VIGUMU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946791646844","data":{"timestamp":" 946791646844"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_083053"," gameId":" 18bf14a0-8260-4c05-bdde-ffdcb6f26518"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Haikuwa vigumu kupata chakula milimani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUPATA"," userResponse":" KUPATA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946791647673","data":{"timestamp":" 946791647671"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_083053"," gameId":" 18bf14a0-8260-4c05-bdde-ffdcb6f26518"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Haikuwa vigumu kupata chakula milimani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHAKULA"," userResponse":" CHAKULA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946791648839","data":{"timestamp":" 946791648838"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_083053"," gameId":" 18bf14a0-8260-4c05-bdde-ffdcb6f26518"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Haikuwa vigumu kupata chakula milimani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MILIMANI"," userResponse":" MILIMANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946791651836","data":{"timestamp":" 946791651836"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_083053"," gameId":" 18bf14a0-8260-4c05-bdde-ffdcb6f26518"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Haikuwa vigumu kupata chakula milimani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HAIKUWA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946791653456","data":{"timestamp":" 946791653456"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_083053"," gameId":" 18bf14a0-8260-4c05-bdde-ffdcb6f26518"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Haikuwa vigumu kupata chakula milimani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VIGUMU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946791655296","data":{"timestamp":" 946791655296"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_083053"," gameId":" 18bf14a0-8260-4c05-bdde-ffdcb6f26518"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Haikuwa vigumu kupata chakula milimani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUPATA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946791657345","data":{"timestamp":" 946791657345"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_083053"," gameId":" 18bf14a0-8260-4c05-bdde-ffdcb6f26518"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Haikuwa vigumu kupata chakula milimani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHAKULA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946791659588","data":{"timestamp":" 946791659587"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_083053"," gameId":" 18bf14a0-8260-4c05-bdde-ffdcb6f26518"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Haikuwa vigumu kupata chakula milimani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MILIMANI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946791661993","data":{"timestamp":" 946791661993"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_083053"," gameId":" 18bf14a0-8260-4c05-bdde-ffdcb6f26518"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Vichaka vilimea katikati mwa pengo za miamba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VICHAKA"," userResponse":" VICHAKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946791662887","data":{"timestamp":" 946791662887"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_083053"," gameId":" 18bf14a0-8260-4c05-bdde-ffdcb6f26518"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Vichaka vilimea katikati mwa pengo za miamba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VILIMEA"," userResponse":" VILIMEA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946791663950","data":{"timestamp":" 946791663950"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_083053"," gameId":" 18bf14a0-8260-4c05-bdde-ffdcb6f26518"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Vichaka vilimea katikati mwa pengo za miamba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KATIKATI"," userResponse":" KATIKATI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946791664278","data":{"timestamp":" 946791664277"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_083053"," gameId":" 18bf14a0-8260-4c05-bdde-ffdcb6f26518"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Vichaka vilimea katikati mwa pengo za miamba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MWA"," userResponse":" MWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946791664914","data":{"timestamp":" 946791664913"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_083053"," gameId":" 18bf14a0-8260-4c05-bdde-ffdcb6f26518"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Vichaka vilimea katikati mwa pengo za miamba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PENGO"," userResponse":" PENGO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946791665179","data":{"timestamp":" 946791665179"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_083053"," gameId":" 18bf14a0-8260-4c05-bdde-ffdcb6f26518"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Vichaka vilimea katikati mwa pengo za miamba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZA"," userResponse":" ZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946791665978","data":{"timestamp":" 946791665977"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_083053"," gameId":" 18bf14a0-8260-4c05-bdde-ffdcb6f26518"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Vichaka vilimea katikati mwa pengo za miamba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MIAMBA"," userResponse":" MIAMBA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946791669292","data":{"timestamp":" 946791669292"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_083053"," gameId":" 18bf14a0-8260-4c05-bdde-ffdcb6f26518"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Vichaka vilimea katikati mwa pengo za miamba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VICHAKA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946791671475","data":{"timestamp":" 946791671475"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_083053"," gameId":" 18bf14a0-8260-4c05-bdde-ffdcb6f26518"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Vichaka vilimea katikati mwa pengo za miamba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VILIMEA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946791675008","data":{"timestamp":" 946791675008"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_083053"," gameId":" 18bf14a0-8260-4c05-bdde-ffdcb6f26518"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Vichaka vilimea katikati mwa pengo za miamba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KATIKATI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946791676518","data":{"timestamp":" 946791676518"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_083053"," gameId":" 18bf14a0-8260-4c05-bdde-ffdcb6f26518"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Vichaka vilimea katikati mwa pengo za miamba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MWA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946791678845","data":{"timestamp":" 946791678845"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_083053"," gameId":" 18bf14a0-8260-4c05-bdde-ffdcb6f26518"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Vichaka vilimea katikati mwa pengo za miamba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PENGO"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946791680404","data":{"timestamp":" 946791680403"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_083053"," gameId":" 18bf14a0-8260-4c05-bdde-ffdcb6f26518"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Vichaka vilimea katikati mwa pengo za miamba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946791685017","data":{"timestamp":" 946791685017"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_083053"," gameId":" 18bf14a0-8260-4c05-bdde-ffdcb6f26518"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Vichaka vilimea katikati mwa pengo za miamba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MIAMBA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946791686857","data":{"timestamp":" 946791686857"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_083053"," gameId":" 18bf14a0-8260-4c05-bdde-ffdcb6f26518"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Miti ilimea kwenye mitelemko ya milima."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MITI"," userResponse":" MITI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946791687662","data":{"timestamp":" 946791687662"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_083053"," gameId":" 18bf14a0-8260-4c05-bdde-ffdcb6f26518"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Miti ilimea kwenye mitelemko ya milima."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ILIMEA"," userResponse":" ILIMEA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946791688165","data":{"timestamp":" 946791688164"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_083053"," gameId":" 18bf14a0-8260-4c05-bdde-ffdcb6f26518"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Miti ilimea kwenye mitelemko ya milima."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWENYE"," userResponse":" KWENYE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946791689348","data":{"timestamp":" 946791689348"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_083053"," gameId":" 18bf14a0-8260-4c05-bdde-ffdcb6f26518"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Miti ilimea kwenye mitelemko ya milima."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MITELEMKO"," userResponse":" MITELEMKO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946791689591","data":{"timestamp":" 946791689591"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_083053"," gameId":" 18bf14a0-8260-4c05-bdde-ffdcb6f26518"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Miti ilimea kwenye mitelemko ya milima."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946791690411","data":{"timestamp":" 946791690410"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_083053"," gameId":" 18bf14a0-8260-4c05-bdde-ffdcb6f26518"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Miti ilimea kwenye mitelemko ya milima."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MILIMA"," userResponse":" MILIMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946791693096","data":{"timestamp":" 946791693096"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_083053"," gameId":" 18bf14a0-8260-4c05-bdde-ffdcb6f26518"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Miti ilimea kwenye mitelemko ya milima."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MITI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946791695088","data":{"timestamp":" 946791695088"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_083053"," gameId":" 18bf14a0-8260-4c05-bdde-ffdcb6f26518"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Miti ilimea kwenye mitelemko ya milima."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ILIMEA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946791696736","data":{"timestamp":" 946791696735"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_083053"," gameId":" 18bf14a0-8260-4c05-bdde-ffdcb6f26518"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Miti ilimea kwenye mitelemko ya milima."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWENYE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946791698775","data":{"timestamp":" 946791698775"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_083053"," gameId":" 18bf14a0-8260-4c05-bdde-ffdcb6f26518"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Miti ilimea kwenye mitelemko ya milima."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MITELEMKO"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946791700426","data":{"timestamp":" 946791700426"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_083053"," gameId":" 18bf14a0-8260-4c05-bdde-ffdcb6f26518"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Miti ilimea kwenye mitelemko ya milima."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946791702249","data":{"timestamp":" 946791702248"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_083053"," gameId":" 18bf14a0-8260-4c05-bdde-ffdcb6f26518"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Miti ilimea kwenye mitelemko ya milima."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MILIMA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946791704220","data":{"timestamp":" 946791704219"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_083053"," gameId":" 18bf14a0-8260-4c05-bdde-ffdcb6f26518"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wazazi walitega sungura wa miambani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAZAZI"," userResponse":" WAZAZI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946791705286","data":{"timestamp":" 946791705286"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_083053"," gameId":" 18bf14a0-8260-4c05-bdde-ffdcb6f26518"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wazazi walitega sungura wa miambani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALITEGA"," userResponse":" WALITEGA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946791706180","data":{"timestamp":" 946791706180"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_083053"," gameId":" 18bf14a0-8260-4c05-bdde-ffdcb6f26518"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wazazi walitega sungura wa miambani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SUNGURA"," userResponse":" SUNGURA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946791706332","data":{"timestamp":" 946791706332"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_083053"," gameId":" 18bf14a0-8260-4c05-bdde-ffdcb6f26518"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wazazi walitega sungura wa miambani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WA"," userResponse":" WA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946791707356","data":{"timestamp":" 946791707356"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_083053"," gameId":" 18bf14a0-8260-4c05-bdde-ffdcb6f26518"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wazazi walitega sungura wa miambani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MIAMBANI"," userResponse":" MIAMBANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946791711973","data":{"timestamp":" 946791711973"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_083053"," gameId":" 18bf14a0-8260-4c05-bdde-ffdcb6f26518"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wazazi walitega sungura wa miambani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAZAZI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946791714171","data":{"timestamp":" 946791714170"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_083053"," gameId":" 18bf14a0-8260-4c05-bdde-ffdcb6f26518"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wazazi walitega sungura wa miambani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALITEGA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946791716452","data":{"timestamp":" 946791716452"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_083053"," gameId":" 18bf14a0-8260-4c05-bdde-ffdcb6f26518"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wazazi walitega sungura wa miambani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SUNGURA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946791718183","data":{"timestamp":" 946791718183"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_083053"," gameId":" 18bf14a0-8260-4c05-bdde-ffdcb6f26518"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wazazi walitega sungura wa miambani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946791720152","data":{"timestamp":" 946791720152"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_083053"," gameId":" 18bf14a0-8260-4c05-bdde-ffdcb6f26518"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wazazi walitega sungura wa miambani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MIAMBANI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946791722229","data":{"timestamp":" 946791722228"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_083053"," gameId":" 18bf14a0-8260-4c05-bdde-ffdcb6f26518"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watoto walishika ndege."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WATOTO"," userResponse":" WATOTO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946791723253","data":{"timestamp":" 946791723252"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_083053"," gameId":" 18bf14a0-8260-4c05-bdde-ffdcb6f26518"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watoto walishika ndege."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALISHIKA"," userResponse":" WALISHIKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946791723856","data":{"timestamp":" 946791723856"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_083053"," gameId":" 18bf14a0-8260-4c05-bdde-ffdcb6f26518"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watoto walishika ndege."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NDEGE"," userResponse":" NDEGE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946791726727","data":{"timestamp":" 946791726727"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_083053"," gameId":" 18bf14a0-8260-4c05-bdde-ffdcb6f26518"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watoto walishika ndege."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WATOTO"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946791729118","data":{"timestamp":" 946791729118"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_083053"," gameId":" 18bf14a0-8260-4c05-bdde-ffdcb6f26518"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watoto walishika ndege."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALISHIKA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946791730865","data":{"timestamp":" 946791730864"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_083053"," gameId":" 18bf14a0-8260-4c05-bdde-ffdcb6f26518"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watoto walishika ndege."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NDEGE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946791733365","data":{"timestamp":" 946791733365"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_083053"," gameId":" 18bf14a0-8260-4c05-bdde-ffdcb6f26518"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Familia zingine ziliona jinsi familia ya milimani ilivyoishi vizuri."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" FAMILIA"," userResponse":" FAMILIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946791734299","data":{"timestamp":" 946791734299"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_083053"," gameId":" 18bf14a0-8260-4c05-bdde-ffdcb6f26518"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Familia zingine ziliona jinsi familia ya milimani ilivyoishi vizuri."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZINGINE"," userResponse":" ZINGINE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946791735662","data":{"timestamp":" 946791735662"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_083053"," gameId":" 18bf14a0-8260-4c05-bdde-ffdcb6f26518"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Familia zingine ziliona jinsi familia ya milimani ilivyoishi vizuri."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZILIONA"," userResponse":" ZILIONA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946791736265","data":{"timestamp":" 946791736265"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_083053"," gameId":" 18bf14a0-8260-4c05-bdde-ffdcb6f26518"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Familia zingine ziliona jinsi familia ya milimani ilivyoishi vizuri."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JINSI"," userResponse":" JINSI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946791737047","data":{"timestamp":" 946791737047"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_083053"," gameId":" 18bf14a0-8260-4c05-bdde-ffdcb6f26518"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Familia zingine ziliona jinsi familia ya milimani ilivyoishi vizuri."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" FAMILIA"," userResponse":" FAMILIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946791737300","data":{"timestamp":" 946791737299"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_083053"," gameId":" 18bf14a0-8260-4c05-bdde-ffdcb6f26518"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Familia zingine ziliona jinsi familia ya milimani ilivyoishi vizuri."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946791738195","data":{"timestamp":" 946791738195"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_083053"," gameId":" 18bf14a0-8260-4c05-bdde-ffdcb6f26518"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Familia zingine ziliona jinsi familia ya milimani ilivyoishi vizuri."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MILIMANI"," userResponse":" MILIMANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946791739193","data":{"timestamp":" 946791739192"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_083053"," gameId":" 18bf14a0-8260-4c05-bdde-ffdcb6f26518"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Familia zingine ziliona jinsi familia ya milimani ilivyoishi vizuri."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ILIVYOISHI"," userResponse":" ILIVYOISHI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946791740380","data":{"timestamp":" 946791740379"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_083053"," gameId":" 18bf14a0-8260-4c05-bdde-ffdcb6f26518"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Familia zingine ziliona jinsi familia ya milimani ilivyoishi vizuri."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VIZURI"," userResponse":" VIZURI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946791743206","data":{"timestamp":" 946791743205"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_083053"," gameId":" 18bf14a0-8260-4c05-bdde-ffdcb6f26518"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Familia zingine ziliona jinsi familia ya milimani ilivyoishi vizuri."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" FAMILIA"," userResponse":" START_FAMILIA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946791744502","data":{"timestamp":" 946791744502"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_083053"," gameId":" 18bf14a0-8260-4c05-bdde-ffdcb6f26518"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Familia zingine ziliona jinsi familia ya milimani ilivyoishi vizuri."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" FAMILIA"," userResponse":" START_FAMILIA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946791746256","data":{"timestamp":" 946791746256"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_083053"," gameId":" 18bf14a0-8260-4c05-bdde-ffdcb6f26518"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Familia zingine ziliona jinsi familia ya milimani ilivyoishi vizuri."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" FAMILIA"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946791748307","data":{"timestamp":" 946791748307"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_083053"," gameId":" 18bf14a0-8260-4c05-bdde-ffdcb6f26518"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Familia zingine ziliona jinsi familia ya milimani ilivyoishi vizuri."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZINGINE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946791751575","data":{"timestamp":" 946791751574"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_083053"," gameId":" 18bf14a0-8260-4c05-bdde-ffdcb6f26518"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Familia zingine ziliona jinsi familia ya milimani ilivyoishi vizuri."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZILIONA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946791753484","data":{"timestamp":" 946791753484"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_083053"," gameId":" 18bf14a0-8260-4c05-bdde-ffdcb6f26518"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Familia zingine ziliona jinsi familia ya milimani ilivyoishi vizuri."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JINSI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946791755493","data":{"timestamp":" 946791755492"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_083053"," gameId":" 18bf14a0-8260-4c05-bdde-ffdcb6f26518"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Familia zingine ziliona jinsi familia ya milimani ilivyoishi vizuri."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" FAMILIA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946791757137","data":{"timestamp":" 946791757137"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_083053"," gameId":" 18bf14a0-8260-4c05-bdde-ffdcb6f26518"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Familia zingine ziliona jinsi familia ya milimani ilivyoishi vizuri."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946791759140","data":{"timestamp":" 946791759140"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_083053"," gameId":" 18bf14a0-8260-4c05-bdde-ffdcb6f26518"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Familia zingine ziliona jinsi familia ya milimani ilivyoishi vizuri."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MILIMANI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946791761777","data":{"timestamp":" 946791761777"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_083053"," gameId":" 18bf14a0-8260-4c05-bdde-ffdcb6f26518"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Familia zingine ziliona jinsi familia ya milimani ilivyoishi vizuri."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ILIVYOISHI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946791763608","data":{"timestamp":" 946791763608"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_083053"," gameId":" 18bf14a0-8260-4c05-bdde-ffdcb6f26518"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Familia zingine ziliona jinsi familia ya milimani ilivyoishi vizuri."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VIZURI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946791765519","data":{"timestamp":" 946791765518"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_083053"," gameId":" 18bf14a0-8260-4c05-bdde-ffdcb6f26518"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lazima mje huko pia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAISHA"," userResponse":" MAISHA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946791765742","data":{"timestamp":" 946791765742"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_083053"," gameId":" 18bf14a0-8260-4c05-bdde-ffdcb6f26518"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lazima mje huko pia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946791765876","data":{"timestamp":" 946791765875"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_083053"," gameId":" 18bf14a0-8260-4c05-bdde-ffdcb6f26518"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Lazima mje huko pia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946791765958","data":{"timestamp":" 946791765958"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_083053"," gameId":" 18bf14a0-8260-4c05-bdde-ffdcb6f26518"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lazima mje huko pia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"num.scale:72..82.off1.11__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946791773781","data":{"timestamp":" 946791773781"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_083053"," gameId":" 18bf14a0-8260-4c05-bdde-ffdcb6f26518"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Lazima mje huko pia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::HF.wrd.len-8.rand.12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946791782094","data":{"timestamp":" 946791782094"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_083053"," gameId":" 18bf14a0-8260-4c05-bdde-ffdcb6f26518"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Lazima mje huko pia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946791787351","data":{"timestamp":" 946791787351"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_083053"," gameId":" 18bf14a0-8260-4c05-bdde-ffdcb6f26518"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Lazima mje huko pia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.len-8.9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946791803467","data":{"timestamp":" 946791803467"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_083053"," gameId":" fd9a8578-c48f-4217-bfdf-f18a22288a37"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.len-8.9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_saba"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" s"," userResponse":" s"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.len-8.9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946791804652","data":{"timestamp":" 946791804652"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_083053"," gameId":" fd9a8578-c48f-4217-bfdf-f18a22288a37"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.len-8.9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_saba"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" a"," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.len-8.9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946791806111","data":{"timestamp":" 946791806111"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_083053"," gameId":" fd9a8578-c48f-4217-bfdf-f18a22288a37"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.len-8.9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_saba"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" b"," userResponse":" b"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.len-8.9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946791807711","data":{"timestamp":" 946791807711"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_083053"," gameId":" fd9a8578-c48f-4217-bfdf-f18a22288a37"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.len-8.9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_saba"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" a"," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.len-8.9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946791821676","data":{"timestamp":" 946791821676"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_083053"," gameId":" fd9a8578-c48f-4217-bfdf-f18a22288a37"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.len-8.9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_niruhusu"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" n"," userResponse":" n"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.len-8.9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946791823521","data":{"timestamp":" 946791823521"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_083053"," gameId":" fd9a8578-c48f-4217-bfdf-f18a22288a37"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.len-8.9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_niruhusu"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" i"," userResponse":" i"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.len-8.9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946791826806","data":{"timestamp":" 946791826806"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_083053"," gameId":" fd9a8578-c48f-4217-bfdf-f18a22288a37"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.len-8.9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_niruhusu"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" r"," userResponse":" r"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.len-8.9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946791829730","data":{"timestamp":" 946791829730"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_083053"," gameId":" fd9a8578-c48f-4217-bfdf-f18a22288a37"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.len-8.9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_niruhusu"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" u"," userResponse":" u"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.len-8.9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946791833571","data":{"timestamp":" 946791833571"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_083053"," gameId":" fd9a8578-c48f-4217-bfdf-f18a22288a37"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.len-8.9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_niruhusu"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" h"," userResponse":" h"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.len-8.9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946791835896","data":{"timestamp":" 946791835895"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_083053"," gameId":" fd9a8578-c48f-4217-bfdf-f18a22288a37"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.len-8.9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_niruhusu"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" u"," userResponse":" u"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.len-8.9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946791840274","data":{"timestamp":" 946791840274"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_083053"," gameId":" fd9a8578-c48f-4217-bfdf-f18a22288a37"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.len-8.9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_niruhusu"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" s"," userResponse":" s"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.len-8.9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946791842598","data":{"timestamp":" 946791842598"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_083053"," gameId":" fd9a8578-c48f-4217-bfdf-f18a22288a37"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.len-8.9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_niruhusu"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" u"," userResponse":" u"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.len-8.9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946791849949","data":{"timestamp":" 946791849949"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_083053"," gameId":" fd9a8578-c48f-4217-bfdf-f18a22288a37"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.len-8.9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" write_niruhusu"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"num.scale:72..82.off1.11__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946791855596","data":{"timestamp":" 946791855596"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_083053"," gameId":" fd9a8578-c48f-4217-bfdf-f18a22288a37"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.len-8.9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" write_niruhusu"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946791861958","data":{"timestamp":" 946791861957"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_083053"," gameId":" fd9a8578-c48f-4217-bfdf-f18a22288a37"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.len-8.9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" write_niruhusu"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946791867740","data":{"timestamp":" 946791867740"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_083053"," gameId":" fd9a8578-c48f-4217-bfdf-f18a22288a37"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.len-8.9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" write_niruhusu"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946791873567","data":{"timestamp":" 946791873567"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_083053"," gameId":" fd9a8578-c48f-4217-bfdf-f18a22288a37"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.len-8.9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" write_niruhusu"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"num.scale:72..82.off1.11__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946791878458","data":{"timestamp":" 946791878458"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_083053"," gameId":" fd9a8578-c48f-4217-bfdf-f18a22288a37"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.len-8.9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" write_niruhusu"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946791889584","data":{"timestamp":" 946791889583"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_083053"," gameId":" fd9a8578-c48f-4217-bfdf-f18a22288a37"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.len-8.9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" write_niruhusu"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946791898101","data":{"timestamp":" 946791898100"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_083053"," gameId":" ee7a58be-380d-4eb2-840c-1c8e1eccdf77"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MBUGA"," userResponse":" MBUGA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946791898332","data":{"timestamp":" 946791898332"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_083053"," gameId":" ee7a58be-380d-4eb2-840c-1c8e1eccdf77"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZA"," userResponse":" ZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946791899308","data":{"timestamp":" 946791899308"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_083053"," gameId":" ee7a58be-380d-4eb2-840c-1c8e1eccdf77"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WANYAMA"," userResponse":" WANYAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946791900592","data":{"timestamp":" 946791900591"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_083053"," gameId":" ee7a58be-380d-4eb2-840c-1c8e1eccdf77"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TANZANIA"," userResponse":" TANZANIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946791903538","data":{"timestamp":" 946791903537"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_083053"," gameId":" ee7a58be-380d-4eb2-840c-1c8e1eccdf77"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946791904390","data":{"timestamp":" 946791904389"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_083053"," gameId":" ee7a58be-380d-4eb2-840c-1c8e1eccdf77"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWANZA"," userResponse":" KWANZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946791904709","data":{"timestamp":" 946791904709"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_083053"," gameId":" ee7a58be-380d-4eb2-840c-1c8e1eccdf77"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946791905953","data":{"timestamp":" 946791905953"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_083053"," gameId":" ee7a58be-380d-4eb2-840c-1c8e1eccdf77"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SERENGETI"," userResponse":" SERENGETI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946791909450","data":{"timestamp":" 946791909450"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_083053"," gameId":" ee7a58be-380d-4eb2-840c-1c8e1eccdf77"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngorongoro Manyara na Mikumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NGORONGORO"," userResponse":" NGORONGORO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946791910444","data":{"timestamp":" 946791910444"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_083053"," gameId":" ee7a58be-380d-4eb2-840c-1c8e1eccdf77"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngorongoro Manyara na Mikumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MANYARA"," userResponse":" MANYARA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946791910713","data":{"timestamp":" 946791910712"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_083053"," gameId":" ee7a58be-380d-4eb2-840c-1c8e1eccdf77"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngorongoro Manyara na Mikumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946791911666","data":{"timestamp":" 946791911666"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_083053"," gameId":" ee7a58be-380d-4eb2-840c-1c8e1eccdf77"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngorongoro Manyara na Mikumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MIKUMI"," userResponse":" MIKUMI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946791914541","data":{"timestamp":" 946791914540"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_083053"," gameId":" ee7a58be-380d-4eb2-840c-1c8e1eccdf77"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" O"," userResponse":" O"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946791915581","data":{"timestamp":" 946791915581"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_083053"," gameId":" ee7a58be-380d-4eb2-840c-1c8e1eccdf77"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TANZANIA"," userResponse":" TANZANIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946791916060","data":{"timestamp":" 946791916059"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_083053"," gameId":" ee7a58be-380d-4eb2-840c-1c8e1eccdf77"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" OYEE"," userResponse":" OYEE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946791920490","data":{"timestamp":" 946791920490"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_083053"," gameId":" ee7a58be-380d-4eb2-840c-1c8e1eccdf77"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" songs"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946791920561","data":{"timestamp":" 946791920561"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_083053"," gameId":" ee7a58be-380d-4eb2-840c-1c8e1eccdf77"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" OYEE"," userResponse":" OYEE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946791926367","data":{"timestamp":" 946791926367"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_083053"," gameId":" ee7a58be-380d-4eb2-840c-1c8e1eccdf77"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" songs"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"num.scale:72..82.off1.11__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946791932176","data":{"timestamp":" 946791932176"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_083053"," gameId":" ee7a58be-380d-4eb2-840c-1c8e1eccdf77"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" songs"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946791937722","data":{"timestamp":" 946791937722"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_083053"," gameId":" ee7a58be-380d-4eb2-840c-1c8e1eccdf77"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" songs"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946791942988","data":{"timestamp":" 946791942987"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_083053"," gameId":" ee7a58be-380d-4eb2-840c-1c8e1eccdf77"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" songs"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946791948415","data":{"timestamp":" 946791948415"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_083053"," gameId":" ee7a58be-380d-4eb2-840c-1c8e1eccdf77"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" songs"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"num.scale:72..82.off1.11__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946791954912","data":{"timestamp":" 946791954911"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_083053"," gameId":" ee7a58be-380d-4eb2-840c-1c8e1eccdf77"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" songs"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946791961009","data":{"timestamp":" 946791961009"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_083053"," gameId":" ee7a58be-380d-4eb2-840c-1c8e1eccdf77"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" songs"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946791967430","data":{"timestamp":" 946791967430"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_083053"," gameId":" ee7a58be-380d-4eb2-840c-1c8e1eccdf77"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" songs"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946791979543","data":{"timestamp":" 946791979542"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_083053"," gameId":" a35ca7fb-a02b-442d-acee-17f50c0c56dd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_alicheza"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" a"," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946791980706","data":{"timestamp":" 946791980706"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_083053"," gameId":" a35ca7fb-a02b-442d-acee-17f50c0c56dd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_alicheza"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" li"," userResponse":" li"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946791981613","data":{"timestamp":" 946791981613"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_083053"," gameId":" a35ca7fb-a02b-442d-acee-17f50c0c56dd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_alicheza"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" che"," userResponse":" che"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946791981935","data":{"timestamp":" 946791981935"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_083053"," gameId":" a35ca7fb-a02b-442d-acee-17f50c0c56dd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_alicheza"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" za"," userResponse":" za"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946791986846","data":{"timestamp":" 946791986846"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_083053"," gameId":" a35ca7fb-a02b-442d-acee-17f50c0c56dd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_wakitembea"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" wa"," userResponse":" wa"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946791988026","data":{"timestamp":" 946791988026"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_083053"," gameId":" a35ca7fb-a02b-442d-acee-17f50c0c56dd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_wakitembea"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ki"," userResponse":" ki"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946791990294","data":{"timestamp":" 946791990294"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_083053"," gameId":" a35ca7fb-a02b-442d-acee-17f50c0c56dd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_wakitembea"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" te"," userResponse":" te"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946791991311","data":{"timestamp":" 946791991311"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_083053"," gameId":" a35ca7fb-a02b-442d-acee-17f50c0c56dd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_wakitembea"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" mbe"," userResponse":" mbe"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946791991761","data":{"timestamp":" 946791991761"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_083053"," gameId":" a35ca7fb-a02b-442d-acee-17f50c0c56dd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_wakitembea"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" a"," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946791996910","data":{"timestamp":" 946791996910"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_083053"," gameId":" a35ca7fb-a02b-442d-acee-17f50c0c56dd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_hospitali"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ho"," userResponse":" ho"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946791998352","data":{"timestamp":" 946791998352"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_083053"," gameId":" a35ca7fb-a02b-442d-acee-17f50c0c56dd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_hospitali"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" s"," userResponse":" s"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946792000587","data":{"timestamp":" 946792000587"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_083053"," gameId":" a35ca7fb-a02b-442d-acee-17f50c0c56dd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_hospitali"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" pi"," userResponse":" pi"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946792002617","data":{"timestamp":" 946792002617"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_083053"," gameId":" a35ca7fb-a02b-442d-acee-17f50c0c56dd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_hospitali"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ta"," userResponse":" ta"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946792003006","data":{"timestamp":" 946792003006"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_083053"," gameId":" a35ca7fb-a02b-442d-acee-17f50c0c56dd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_hospitali"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" li"," userResponse":" li"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946792008096","data":{"timestamp":" 946792008096"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_083053"," gameId":" a35ca7fb-a02b-442d-acee-17f50c0c56dd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_parachichi"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" pa"," userResponse":" pa"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946792008646","data":{"timestamp":" 946792008646"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_083053"," gameId":" a35ca7fb-a02b-442d-acee-17f50c0c56dd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_parachichi"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ra"," userResponse":" ra"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946792009206","data":{"timestamp":" 946792009206"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_083053"," gameId":" a35ca7fb-a02b-442d-acee-17f50c0c56dd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_parachichi"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" chi"," userResponse":" chi"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946792009580","data":{"timestamp":" 946792009580"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_083053"," gameId":" a35ca7fb-a02b-442d-acee-17f50c0c56dd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_parachichi"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" chi"," userResponse":" chi"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946792013683","data":{"timestamp":" 946792013682"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_083053"," gameId":" a35ca7fb-a02b-442d-acee-17f50c0c56dd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_tikitimaji"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ti"," userResponse":" ti"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946792015382","data":{"timestamp":" 946792015381"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_083053"," gameId":" a35ca7fb-a02b-442d-acee-17f50c0c56dd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_tikitimaji"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ki"," userResponse":" ti"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946792021597","data":{"timestamp":" 946792021596"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_083053"," gameId":" a35ca7fb-a02b-442d-acee-17f50c0c56dd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_tikitimaji"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" ki"," userResponse":" ki"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946792024596","data":{"timestamp":" 946792024595"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_083053"," gameId":" a35ca7fb-a02b-442d-acee-17f50c0c56dd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_tikitimaji"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ti"," userResponse":" ma"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946792030903","data":{"timestamp":" 946792030903"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_083053"," gameId":" a35ca7fb-a02b-442d-acee-17f50c0c56dd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_tikitimaji"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" ti"," userResponse":" ti"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946792031685","data":{"timestamp":" 946792031685"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_083053"," gameId":" a35ca7fb-a02b-442d-acee-17f50c0c56dd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_tikitimaji"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ma"," userResponse":" ji"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946792038342","data":{"timestamp":" 946792038342"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_083053"," gameId":" a35ca7fb-a02b-442d-acee-17f50c0c56dd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_tikitimaji"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" ma"," userResponse":" ma"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946792039123","data":{"timestamp":" 946792039123"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_083053"," gameId":" a35ca7fb-a02b-442d-acee-17f50c0c56dd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_tikitimaji"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ji"," userResponse":" ji"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946792042973","data":{"timestamp":" 946792042972"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_083053"," gameId":" a35ca7fb-a02b-442d-acee-17f50c0c56dd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_kitunguu"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ki"," userResponse":" ki"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946792043608","data":{"timestamp":" 946792043608"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_083053"," gameId":" a35ca7fb-a02b-442d-acee-17f50c0c56dd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_kitunguu"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" tu"," userResponse":" tu"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946792044688","data":{"timestamp":" 946792044687"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_083053"," gameId":" a35ca7fb-a02b-442d-acee-17f50c0c56dd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_kitunguu"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ngu"," userResponse":" ngu"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946792044983","data":{"timestamp":" 946792044983"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_083053"," gameId":" a35ca7fb-a02b-442d-acee-17f50c0c56dd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_kitunguu"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" u"," userResponse":" u"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946792050251","data":{"timestamp":" 946792050251"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_083053"," gameId":" a35ca7fb-a02b-442d-acee-17f50c0c56dd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_anakula"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" a"," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946792050997","data":{"timestamp":" 946792050996"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_083053"," gameId":" a35ca7fb-a02b-442d-acee-17f50c0c56dd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_anakula"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" na"," userResponse":" na"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946792052595","data":{"timestamp":" 946792052595"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_083053"," gameId":" a35ca7fb-a02b-442d-acee-17f50c0c56dd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_anakula"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ku"," userResponse":" ku"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946792052925","data":{"timestamp":" 946792052924"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_083053"," gameId":" a35ca7fb-a02b-442d-acee-17f50c0c56dd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_anakula"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" la"," userResponse":" la"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946792058999","data":{"timestamp":" 946792058999"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_083053"," gameId":" a35ca7fb-a02b-442d-acee-17f50c0c56dd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_kuchakuro"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ku"," userResponse":" ku"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946792060214","data":{"timestamp":" 946792060214"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_083053"," gameId":" a35ca7fb-a02b-442d-acee-17f50c0c56dd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_kuchakuro"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" cha"," userResponse":" cha"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946792061487","data":{"timestamp":" 946792061487"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_083053"," gameId":" a35ca7fb-a02b-442d-acee-17f50c0c56dd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_kuchakuro"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ku"," userResponse":" ku"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946792062377","data":{"timestamp":" 946792062377"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_083053"," gameId":" a35ca7fb-a02b-442d-acee-17f50c0c56dd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_kuchakuro"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ro"," userResponse":" ro"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946792071696","data":{"timestamp":" 946792071696"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_083053"," gameId":" a35ca7fb-a02b-442d-acee-17f50c0c56dd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_katikati"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ka"," userResponse":" ka"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946792072860","data":{"timestamp":" 946792072860"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_083053"," gameId":" a35ca7fb-a02b-442d-acee-17f50c0c56dd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_katikati"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ti"," userResponse":" ti"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946792073998","data":{"timestamp":" 946792073998"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_083053"," gameId":" a35ca7fb-a02b-442d-acee-17f50c0c56dd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_katikati"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ka"," userResponse":" ti"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946792080052","data":{"timestamp":" 946792080052"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_083053"," gameId":" a35ca7fb-a02b-442d-acee-17f50c0c56dd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_katikati"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" ka"," userResponse":" ka"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946792080655","data":{"timestamp":" 946792080655"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_083053"," gameId":" a35ca7fb-a02b-442d-acee-17f50c0c56dd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_katikati"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ti"," userResponse":" ti"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946792085040","data":{"timestamp":" 946792085040"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_083053"," gameId":" a35ca7fb-a02b-442d-acee-17f50c0c56dd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_familia"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" fa"," userResponse":" fa"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946792086985","data":{"timestamp":" 946792086985"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_083053"," gameId":" a35ca7fb-a02b-442d-acee-17f50c0c56dd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_familia"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" mi"," userResponse":" mi"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946792088998","data":{"timestamp":" 946792088998"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_083053"," gameId":" a35ca7fb-a02b-442d-acee-17f50c0c56dd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_familia"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" li"," userResponse":" li"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946792089871","data":{"timestamp":" 946792089871"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_083053"," gameId":" a35ca7fb-a02b-442d-acee-17f50c0c56dd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_familia"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" a"," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946792091926","data":{"timestamp":" 946792091925"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_083053"," gameId":" a35ca7fb-a02b-442d-acee-17f50c0c56dd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" write_familia"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"place.value:pv-11..99.2D.diff1.8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946792098028","data":{"timestamp":" 946792098028"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_083053"," gameId":" 9f0a54f3-3f99-4bb4-82ce-467bede9ce02"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" countingx"," tutorId":" place.value_pv-11..99.2D.diff1.8"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" 1"," taskName":"  Two digit place value "," problemName":" 73"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" START"," userResponse":" START"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 5"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" tap"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"place.value:pv-11..99.2D.diff1.8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946792112922","data":{"timestamp":" 946792112922"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_083053"," gameId":" 9f0a54f3-3f99-4bb4-82ce-467bede9ce02"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" countingx"," tutorId":" place.value_pv-11..99.2D.diff1.8"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" 1"," taskName":"  Two digit place value "," problemName":" 73"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" END"," userResponse":" END"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 5"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" tap"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"place.value:pv-11..99.2D.diff1.8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946792112924","data":{"timestamp":" 946792112924"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_083053"," gameId":" 9f0a54f3-3f99-4bb4-82ce-467bede9ce02"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" countingx"," tutorId":" place.value_pv-11..99.2D.diff1.8"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" 1"," taskName":"  Two digit place value "," problemName":" 73"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" STARTWRITING"," userResponse":" 1"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 5"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" tap"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"place.value:pv-11..99.2D.diff1.8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946792125720","data":{"timestamp":" 946792125720"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_083053"," gameId":" 9f0a54f3-3f99-4bb4-82ce-467bede9ce02"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" countingx"," tutorId":" place.value_pv-11..99.2D.diff1.8"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" 1"," taskName":"  Two digit place value "," problemName":" 73"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 7"," userResponse":" 7"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 5"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" write"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"place.value:pv-11..99.2D.diff1.8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946792130429","data":{"timestamp":" 946792130429"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_083053"," gameId":" 9f0a54f3-3f99-4bb4-82ce-467bede9ce02"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" countingx"," tutorId":" place.value_pv-11..99.2D.diff1.8"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" 1"," taskName":"  Two digit place value "," problemName":" 73"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 3"," userResponse":" 9"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 5"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" write"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"place.value:pv-11..99.2D.diff1.8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946792137878","data":{"timestamp":" 946792137878"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_083053"," gameId":" 9f0a54f3-3f99-4bb4-82ce-467bede9ce02"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" countingx"," tutorId":" place.value_pv-11..99.2D.diff1.8"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" 1"," taskName":"  Two digit place value "," problemName":" 73"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 3"," userResponse":" 3"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 5"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" write"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"place.value:pv-11..99.2D.diff1.8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946792151219","data":{"timestamp":" 946792151219"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_083053"," gameId":" 9f0a54f3-3f99-4bb4-82ce-467bede9ce02"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" countingx"," tutorId":" place.value_pv-11..99.2D.diff1.8"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" 1"," taskName":"  Two digit place value "," problemName":" 54"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" START"," userResponse":" START"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 5"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" tap"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"place.value:pv-11..99.2D.diff1.8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946792165034","data":{"timestamp":" 946792165033"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_083053"," gameId":" 9f0a54f3-3f99-4bb4-82ce-467bede9ce02"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" countingx"," tutorId":" place.value_pv-11..99.2D.diff1.8"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" 1"," taskName":"  Two digit place value "," problemName":" 54"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" END"," userResponse":" END"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 5"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" tap"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"place.value:pv-11..99.2D.diff1.8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946792165041","data":{"timestamp":" 946792165040"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_083053"," gameId":" 9f0a54f3-3f99-4bb4-82ce-467bede9ce02"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" countingx"," tutorId":" place.value_pv-11..99.2D.diff1.8"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" 1"," taskName":"  Two digit place value "," problemName":" 54"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" STARTWRITING"," userResponse":" 1"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 5"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" tap"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"place.value:pv-11..99.2D.diff1.8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946792175014","data":{"timestamp":" 946792175013"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_083053"," gameId":" 9f0a54f3-3f99-4bb4-82ce-467bede9ce02"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" countingx"," tutorId":" place.value_pv-11..99.2D.diff1.8"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" 1"," taskName":"  Two digit place value "," problemName":" 54"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 5"," userResponse":" 8"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 5"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" write"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"place.value:pv-11..99.2D.diff1.8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946792182024","data":{"timestamp":" 946792182024"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_083053"," gameId":" 9f0a54f3-3f99-4bb4-82ce-467bede9ce02"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" countingx"," tutorId":" place.value_pv-11..99.2D.diff1.8"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" 1"," taskName":"  Two digit place value "," problemName":" 54"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 5"," userResponse":" 5"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 5"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" write"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"place.value:pv-11..99.2D.diff1.8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946792187792","data":{"timestamp":" 946792187792"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_083053"," gameId":" 9f0a54f3-3f99-4bb4-82ce-467bede9ce02"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" countingx"," tutorId":" place.value_pv-11..99.2D.diff1.8"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" 1"," taskName":"  Two digit place value "," problemName":" 54"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 4"," userResponse":" 8"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 5"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" write"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"place.value:pv-11..99.2D.diff1.8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946792193691","data":{"timestamp":" 946792193691"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_083053"," gameId":" 9f0a54f3-3f99-4bb4-82ce-467bede9ce02"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" countingx"," tutorId":" place.value_pv-11..99.2D.diff1.8"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" 1"," taskName":"  Two digit place value "," problemName":" 54"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 4"," userResponse":" 0"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 5"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" write"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"place.value:pv-11..99.2D.diff1.8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946792200660","data":{"timestamp":" 946792200660"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_083053"," gameId":" 9f0a54f3-3f99-4bb4-82ce-467bede9ce02"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" countingx"," tutorId":" place.value_pv-11..99.2D.diff1.8"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" 1"," taskName":"  Two digit place value "," problemName":" 54"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 4"," userResponse":" 8"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 5"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" write"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"place.value:pv-11..99.2D.diff1.8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946792206266","data":{"timestamp":" 946792206266"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_083053"," gameId":" 9f0a54f3-3f99-4bb4-82ce-467bede9ce02"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" countingx"," tutorId":" place.value_pv-11..99.2D.diff1.8"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" 1"," taskName":"  Two digit place value "," problemName":" 54"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 4"," userResponse":" 0"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 5"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" write"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"place.value:pv-11..99.2D.diff1.8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946792213470","data":{"timestamp":" 946792213470"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_083053"," gameId":" 9f0a54f3-3f99-4bb4-82ce-467bede9ce02"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" countingx"," tutorId":" place.value_pv-11..99.2D.diff1.8"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" 1"," taskName":"  Two digit place value "," problemName":" 54"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 4"," userResponse":" 6"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 5"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" write"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"place.value:pv-11..99.2D.diff1.8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946792221676","data":{"timestamp":" 946792221676"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_083053"," gameId":" 9f0a54f3-3f99-4bb4-82ce-467bede9ce02"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" countingx"," tutorId":" place.value_pv-11..99.2D.diff1.8"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" 1"," taskName":"  Two digit place value "," problemName":" 54"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 4"," userResponse":" 6"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 5"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" write"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"place.value:pv-11..99.2D.diff1.8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946792228918","data":{"timestamp":" 946792228918"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_083053"," gameId":" 9f0a54f3-3f99-4bb4-82ce-467bede9ce02"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" countingx"," tutorId":" place.value_pv-11..99.2D.diff1.8"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" 1"," taskName":"  Two digit place value "," problemName":" 54"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 4"," userResponse":" 8"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 5"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" write"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"place.value:pv-11..99.2D.diff1.8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946792237910","data":{"timestamp":" 946792237910"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_083053"," gameId":" 9f0a54f3-3f99-4bb4-82ce-467bede9ce02"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" countingx"," tutorId":" place.value_pv-11..99.2D.diff1.8"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" 1"," taskName":"  Two digit place value "," problemName":" 54"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 4"," userResponse":" 8"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 5"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" write"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"place.value:pv-11..99.2D.diff1.8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946792245443","data":{"timestamp":" 946792245443"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_083053"," gameId":" 9f0a54f3-3f99-4bb4-82ce-467bede9ce02"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" countingx"," tutorId":" place.value_pv-11..99.2D.diff1.8"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" 1"," taskName":"  Two digit place value "," problemName":" 54"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 4"," userResponse":" 0"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 5"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" write"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"place.value:pv-11..99.2D.diff1.8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946792254591","data":{"timestamp":" 946792254590"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_083053"," gameId":" 9f0a54f3-3f99-4bb4-82ce-467bede9ce02"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" countingx"," tutorId":" place.value_pv-11..99.2D.diff1.8"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" 1"," taskName":"  Two digit place value "," problemName":" 54"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 4"," userResponse":" 0"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 5"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" write"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"place.value:pv-11..99.2D.diff1.8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946792259372","data":{"timestamp":" 946792259372"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_083053"," gameId":" 9f0a54f3-3f99-4bb4-82ce-467bede9ce02"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" countingx"," tutorId":" place.value_pv-11..99.2D.diff1.8"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" 1"," taskName":"  Two digit place value "," problemName":" 54"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 4"," userResponse":" 4"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 5"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" write"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"place.value:pv-11..99.2D.diff1.8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946792273162","data":{"timestamp":" 946792273162"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_083053"," gameId":" 9f0a54f3-3f99-4bb4-82ce-467bede9ce02"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" countingx"," tutorId":" place.value_pv-11..99.2D.diff1.8"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" 1"," taskName":"  Two digit place value "," problemName":" 96"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" START"," userResponse":" START"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 5"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" tap"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"place.value:pv-11..99.2D.diff1.8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946792286737","data":{"timestamp":" 946792286736"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_083053"," gameId":" 9f0a54f3-3f99-4bb4-82ce-467bede9ce02"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" countingx"," tutorId":" place.value_pv-11..99.2D.diff1.8"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" 1"," taskName":"  Two digit place value "," problemName":" 96"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" END"," userResponse":" END"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 5"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" tap"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"place.value:pv-11..99.2D.diff1.8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946792286744","data":{"timestamp":" 946792286743"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_083053"," gameId":" 9f0a54f3-3f99-4bb4-82ce-467bede9ce02"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" countingx"," tutorId":" place.value_pv-11..99.2D.diff1.8"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" 1"," taskName":"  Two digit place value "," problemName":" 96"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" STARTWRITING"," userResponse":" 1"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 5"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" tap"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"place.value:pv-11..99.2D.diff1.8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946792297871","data":{"timestamp":" 946792297871"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_083053"," gameId":" 9f0a54f3-3f99-4bb4-82ce-467bede9ce02"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" countingx"," tutorId":" place.value_pv-11..99.2D.diff1.8"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" 1"," taskName":"  Two digit place value "," problemName":" 96"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 9"," userResponse":" 9"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 5"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" write"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"place.value:pv-11..99.2D.diff1.8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946792303492","data":{"timestamp":" 946792303492"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_083053"," gameId":" 9f0a54f3-3f99-4bb4-82ce-467bede9ce02"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" countingx"," tutorId":" place.value_pv-11..99.2D.diff1.8"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" 1"," taskName":"  Two digit place value "," problemName":" 96"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 6"," userResponse":" 6"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 5"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" write"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"place.value:pv-11..99.2D.diff1.8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946792316917","data":{"timestamp":" 946792316917"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_083053"," gameId":" 9f0a54f3-3f99-4bb4-82ce-467bede9ce02"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" countingx"," tutorId":" place.value_pv-11..99.2D.diff1.8"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" 1"," taskName":"  Two digit place value "," problemName":" 79"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" START"," userResponse":" START"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 5"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" tap"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"place.value:pv-11..99.2D.diff1.8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946792334000","data":{"timestamp":" 946792333999"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_083053"," gameId":" 9f0a54f3-3f99-4bb4-82ce-467bede9ce02"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" countingx"," tutorId":" place.value_pv-11..99.2D.diff1.8"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" 1"," taskName":"  Two digit place value "," problemName":" 79"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" END"," userResponse":" END"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 5"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" tap"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"place.value:pv-11..99.2D.diff1.8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946792334013","data":{"timestamp":" 946792334013"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_083053"," gameId":" 9f0a54f3-3f99-4bb4-82ce-467bede9ce02"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" countingx"," tutorId":" place.value_pv-11..99.2D.diff1.8"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" 1"," taskName":"  Two digit place value "," problemName":" 79"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" STARTWRITING"," userResponse":" 1"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 5"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" tap"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"place.value:pv-11..99.2D.diff1.8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946792344900","data":{"timestamp":" 946792344900"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_083053"," gameId":" 9f0a54f3-3f99-4bb4-82ce-467bede9ce02"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" countingx"," tutorId":" place.value_pv-11..99.2D.diff1.8"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" 1"," taskName":"  Two digit place value "," problemName":" 79"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 7"," userResponse":" 7"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 5"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" write"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"place.value:pv-11..99.2D.diff1.8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946792353905","data":{"timestamp":" 946792353905"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_083053"," gameId":" 9f0a54f3-3f99-4bb4-82ce-467bede9ce02"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" countingx"," tutorId":" place.value_pv-11..99.2D.diff1.8"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" 1"," taskName":"  Two digit place value "," problemName":" 79"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 9"," userResponse":" 8"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 5"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" write"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"place.value:pv-11..99.2D.diff1.8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946792360771","data":{"timestamp":" 946792360771"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_083053"," gameId":" 9f0a54f3-3f99-4bb4-82ce-467bede9ce02"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" countingx"," tutorId":" place.value_pv-11..99.2D.diff1.8"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" 1"," taskName":"  Two digit place value "," problemName":" 79"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 9"," userResponse":" 9"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 5"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" write"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"place.value:pv-11..99.2D.diff1.8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946792373954","data":{"timestamp":" 946792373954"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_083053"," gameId":" 9f0a54f3-3f99-4bb4-82ce-467bede9ce02"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" countingx"," tutorId":" place.value_pv-11..99.2D.diff1.8"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" 1"," taskName":"  Two digit place value "," problemName":" 48"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" START"," userResponse":" START"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 5"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" tap"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"place.value:pv-11..99.2D.diff1.8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946792389545","data":{"timestamp":" 946792389544"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_083053"," gameId":" 9f0a54f3-3f99-4bb4-82ce-467bede9ce02"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" countingx"," tutorId":" place.value_pv-11..99.2D.diff1.8"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" 1"," taskName":"  Two digit place value "," problemName":" 48"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" END"," userResponse":" END"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 5"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" tap"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"place.value:pv-11..99.2D.diff1.8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946792389562","data":{"timestamp":" 946792389561"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_083053"," gameId":" 9f0a54f3-3f99-4bb4-82ce-467bede9ce02"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" countingx"," tutorId":" place.value_pv-11..99.2D.diff1.8"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" 1"," taskName":"  Two digit place value "," problemName":" 48"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" STARTWRITING"," userResponse":" 1"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 5"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" tap"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"place.value:pv-11..99.2D.diff1.8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946792402441","data":{"timestamp":" 946792402441"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_083053"," gameId":" 9f0a54f3-3f99-4bb4-82ce-467bede9ce02"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" countingx"," tutorId":" place.value_pv-11..99.2D.diff1.8"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" 1"," taskName":"  Two digit place value "," problemName":" 48"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 4"," userResponse":" 8"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 5"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" write"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"place.value:pv-11..99.2D.diff1.8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946792409699","data":{"timestamp":" 946792409699"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_083053"," gameId":" 9f0a54f3-3f99-4bb4-82ce-467bede9ce02"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" countingx"," tutorId":" place.value_pv-11..99.2D.diff1.8"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" 1"," taskName":"  Two digit place value "," problemName":" 48"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 4"," userResponse":" 0"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 5"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" write"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"place.value:pv-11..99.2D.diff1.8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946792416541","data":{"timestamp":" 946792416541"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_083053"," gameId":" 9f0a54f3-3f99-4bb4-82ce-467bede9ce02"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" countingx"," tutorId":" place.value_pv-11..99.2D.diff1.8"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" 1"," taskName":"  Two digit place value "," problemName":" 48"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 4"," userResponse":" 0"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 5"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" write"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"place.value:pv-11..99.2D.diff1.8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946792422971","data":{"timestamp":" 946792422971"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_083053"," gameId":" 9f0a54f3-3f99-4bb4-82ce-467bede9ce02"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" countingx"," tutorId":" place.value_pv-11..99.2D.diff1.8"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" 1"," taskName":"  Two digit place value "," problemName":" 48"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 4"," userResponse":" 0"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 5"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" write"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"place.value:pv-11..99.2D.diff1.8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946792432650","data":{"timestamp":" 946792432650"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_083053"," gameId":" 9f0a54f3-3f99-4bb4-82ce-467bede9ce02"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" countingx"," tutorId":" place.value_pv-11..99.2D.diff1.8"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" 1"," taskName":"  Two digit place value "," problemName":" 48"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 4"," userResponse":" 5"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 5"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" write"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"place.value:pv-11..99.2D.diff1.8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946792442026","data":{"timestamp":" 946792442026"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_083053"," gameId":" 9f0a54f3-3f99-4bb4-82ce-467bede9ce02"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" countingx"," tutorId":" place.value_pv-11..99.2D.diff1.8"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" 1"," taskName":"  Two digit place value "," problemName":" 48"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 4"," userResponse":" 6"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 5"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" write"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"place.value:pv-11..99.2D.diff1.8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946792456475","data":{"timestamp":" 946792456475"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_083053"," gameId":" 9f0a54f3-3f99-4bb4-82ce-467bede9ce02"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" countingx"," tutorId":" place.value_pv-11..99.2D.diff1.8"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" 1"," taskName":"  Two digit place value "," problemName":" 48"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 4"," userResponse":" 8"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 5"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" write"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"place.value:pv-11..99.2D.diff1.8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946792461619","data":{"timestamp":" 946792461618"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_083053"," gameId":" 9f0a54f3-3f99-4bb4-82ce-467bede9ce02"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" countingx"," tutorId":" place.value_pv-11..99.2D.diff1.8"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" 1"," taskName":"  Two digit place value "," problemName":" 48"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 4"," userResponse":" 5"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 5"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" write"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"place.value:pv-11..99.2D.diff1.8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946792470005","data":{"timestamp":" 946792470005"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_083053"," gameId":" 9f0a54f3-3f99-4bb4-82ce-467bede9ce02"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" countingx"," tutorId":" place.value_pv-11..99.2D.diff1.8"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" 1"," taskName":"  Two digit place value "," problemName":" 48"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 4"," userResponse":" 9"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 5"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" write"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"place.value:pv-11..99.2D.diff1.8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946792475480","data":{"timestamp":" 946792475480"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_083053"," gameId":" 9f0a54f3-3f99-4bb4-82ce-467bede9ce02"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" countingx"," tutorId":" place.value_pv-11..99.2D.diff1.8"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" 1"," taskName":"  Two digit place value "," problemName":" 48"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 4"," userResponse":" 0"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 5"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" write"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"place.value:pv-11..99.2D.diff1.8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946792482867","data":{"timestamp":" 946792482867"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_083053"," gameId":" 9f0a54f3-3f99-4bb4-82ce-467bede9ce02"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" countingx"," tutorId":" place.value_pv-11..99.2D.diff1.8"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" 1"," taskName":"  Two digit place value "," problemName":" 48"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 4"," userResponse":" 3"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 5"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" write"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"place.value:pv-11..99.2D.diff1.8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946792489977","data":{"timestamp":" 946792489977"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_083053"," gameId":" 9f0a54f3-3f99-4bb4-82ce-467bede9ce02"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" countingx"," tutorId":" place.value_pv-11..99.2D.diff1.8"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" 1"," taskName":"  Two digit place value "," problemName":" 48"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 4"," userResponse":" 8"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 5"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" write"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"place.value:pv-11..99.2D.diff1.8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946792495460","data":{"timestamp":" 946792495460"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_083053"," gameId":" 9f0a54f3-3f99-4bb4-82ce-467bede9ce02"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" countingx"," tutorId":" place.value_pv-11..99.2D.diff1.8"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" 1"," taskName":"  Two digit place value "," problemName":" 48"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 4"," userResponse":" 5"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 5"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" write"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"place.value:pv-11..99.2D.diff1.8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946792500012","data":{"timestamp":" 946792500012"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_083053"," gameId":" 9f0a54f3-3f99-4bb4-82ce-467bede9ce02"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" countingx"," tutorId":" place.value_pv-11..99.2D.diff1.8"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" 1"," taskName":"  Two digit place value "," problemName":" 48"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 4"," userResponse":" 0"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 5"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" write"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"place.value:pv-11..99.2D.diff1.8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946792508472","data":{"timestamp":" 946792508472"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_083053"," gameId":" 9f0a54f3-3f99-4bb4-82ce-467bede9ce02"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" countingx"," tutorId":" place.value_pv-11..99.2D.diff1.8"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" 1"," taskName":"  Two digit place value "," problemName":" 48"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 4"," userResponse":" 0"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 5"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" write"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"place.value:pv-11..99.2D.diff1.8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946792516453","data":{"timestamp":" 946792516453"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_083053"," gameId":" 9f0a54f3-3f99-4bb4-82ce-467bede9ce02"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" countingx"," tutorId":" place.value_pv-11..99.2D.diff1.8"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" 1"," taskName":"  Two digit place value "," problemName":" 48"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 4"," userResponse":" 6"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 5"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" write"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"place.value:pv-11..99.2D.diff1.8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946792523244","data":{"timestamp":" 946792523244"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_083053"," gameId":" 9f0a54f3-3f99-4bb4-82ce-467bede9ce02"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" countingx"," tutorId":" place.value_pv-11..99.2D.diff1.8"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" 1"," taskName":"  Two digit place value "," problemName":" 48"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 4"," userResponse":" 0"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 5"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" write"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"place.value:pv-11..99.2D.diff1.8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946792530091","data":{"timestamp":" 946792530091"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_083053"," gameId":" 9f0a54f3-3f99-4bb4-82ce-467bede9ce02"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" countingx"," tutorId":" place.value_pv-11..99.2D.diff1.8"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" 1"," taskName":"  Two digit place value "," problemName":" 48"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 4"," userResponse":" 0"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 5"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" write"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"place.value:pv-11..99.2D.diff1.8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946792533853","data":{"timestamp":" 946792533853"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_083053"," gameId":" 9f0a54f3-3f99-4bb4-82ce-467bede9ce02"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" countingx"," tutorId":" place.value_pv-11..99.2D.diff1.8"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" 1"," taskName":"  Two digit place value "," problemName":" 48"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 4"," userResponse":" 4"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 5"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" write"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"place.value:pv-11..99.2D.diff1.8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946792538475","data":{"timestamp":" 946792538475"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_083053"," gameId":" 9f0a54f3-3f99-4bb4-82ce-467bede9ce02"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" countingx"," tutorId":" place.value_pv-11..99.2D.diff1.8"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" 1"," taskName":"  Two digit place value "," problemName":" 48"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 8"," userResponse":" 8"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 5"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" write"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"place.value:pv-11..99.2D.diff1.8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946792552419","data":{"timestamp":" 946792552419"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_083053"," gameId":" 9f0a54f3-3f99-4bb4-82ce-467bede9ce02"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" countingx"," tutorId":" place.value_pv-11..99.2D.diff1.8"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" 1"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" 48"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946792552601","data":{"timestamp":" 946792552601"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_083053"," gameId":" 9f0a54f3-3f99-4bb4-82ce-467bede9ce02"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" countingx"," tutorId":" place.value_pv-11..99.2D.diff1.8"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" 1"," taskName":"  Two digit place value "," problemName":" 48"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" ENDPROBLEM"," userResponse":" ENDPROBLEM"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 5"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" ENDPROBLEM"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946792564324","data":{"timestamp":" 946792564324"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_083053"," gameId":" a811c20b-75d7-4524-8c1e-39c4c25ff1c1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Je unakumbuka Mbio Kuu kati ya sungura na kobe?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" JE"," userResponse":" SUNGURA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946792565596","data":{"timestamp":" 946792565595"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_083053"," gameId":" a811c20b-75d7-4524-8c1e-39c4c25ff1c1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Je unakumbuka Mbio Kuu kati ya sungura na kobe?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JE"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946792568747","data":{"timestamp":" 946792568747"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_083053"," gameId":" a811c20b-75d7-4524-8c1e-39c4c25ff1c1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Je unakumbuka Mbio Kuu kati ya sungura na kobe?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UNAKUMBUKA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946792570398","data":{"timestamp":" 946792570398"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_083053"," gameId":" a811c20b-75d7-4524-8c1e-39c4c25ff1c1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Je unakumbuka Mbio Kuu kati ya sungura na kobe?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MBIO"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946792571895","data":{"timestamp":" 946792571895"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_083053"," gameId":" a811c20b-75d7-4524-8c1e-39c4c25ff1c1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Je unakumbuka Mbio Kuu kati ya sungura na kobe?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946792573661","data":{"timestamp":" 946792573661"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_083053"," gameId":" a811c20b-75d7-4524-8c1e-39c4c25ff1c1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Je unakumbuka Mbio Kuu kati ya sungura na kobe?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KATI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946792575197","data":{"timestamp":" 946792575197"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_083053"," gameId":" a811c20b-75d7-4524-8c1e-39c4c25ff1c1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Je unakumbuka Mbio Kuu kati ya sungura na kobe?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946792577357","data":{"timestamp":" 946792577357"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_083053"," gameId":" a811c20b-75d7-4524-8c1e-39c4c25ff1c1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Je unakumbuka Mbio Kuu kati ya sungura na kobe?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SUNGURA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946792578980","data":{"timestamp":" 946792578980"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_083053"," gameId":" a811c20b-75d7-4524-8c1e-39c4c25ff1c1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Je unakumbuka Mbio Kuu kati ya sungura na kobe?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946792580192","data":{"timestamp":" 946792580192"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_083053"," gameId":" a811c20b-75d7-4524-8c1e-39c4c25ff1c1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Je unakumbuka Mbio Kuu kati ya sungura na kobe?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946792580344","data":{"timestamp":" 946792580343"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_083053"," gameId":" a811c20b-75d7-4524-8c1e-39c4c25ff1c1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Je unakumbuka Mbio Kuu kati ya sungura na kobe?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946800208244","data":{"timestamp":" 946800208244"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_083053"," gameId":" 2f284f90-75b0-47f7-a8e2-f864bc1141b7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MBUGA"," userResponse":" MBUGA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946800208467","data":{"timestamp":" 946800208467"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_083053"," gameId":" 2f284f90-75b0-47f7-a8e2-f864bc1141b7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZA"," userResponse":" ZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946800209430","data":{"timestamp":" 946800209430"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_083053"," gameId":" 2f284f90-75b0-47f7-a8e2-f864bc1141b7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WANYAMA"," userResponse":" WANYAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946800210704","data":{"timestamp":" 946800210703"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_083053"," gameId":" 2f284f90-75b0-47f7-a8e2-f864bc1141b7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TANZANIA"," userResponse":" TANZANIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946800213571","data":{"timestamp":" 946800213571"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_083053"," gameId":" 2f284f90-75b0-47f7-a8e2-f864bc1141b7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946800214245","data":{"timestamp":" 946800214245"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_083053"," gameId":" 2f284f90-75b0-47f7-a8e2-f864bc1141b7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" songs"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946800214325","data":{"timestamp":" 946800214325"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_083053"," gameId":" 2f284f90-75b0-47f7-a8e2-f864bc1141b7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.8.lc.rand.stat.noShow.10__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946800224974","data":{"timestamp":" 946800224974"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_083053"," gameId":" aacf1f25-7efb-41dc-a59a-07801b345e4f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.8.lc.rand.stat.noShow.10__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_halikuwa_anyamaze-halikuwa-kutokana"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" halikuwa"," userResponse":" anyamaze"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.8.lc.rand.stat.noShow.10__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946800233626","data":{"timestamp":" 946800233626"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_083053"," gameId":" aacf1f25-7efb-41dc-a59a-07801b345e4f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.8.lc.rand.stat.noShow.10__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_halikuwa_anyamaze-halikuwa-kutokana"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" halikuwa"," userResponse":" halikuwa"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.8.lc.rand.stat.noShow.10__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946800235620","data":{"timestamp":" 946800235620"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_083053"," gameId":" aacf1f25-7efb-41dc-a59a-07801b345e4f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.8.lc.rand.stat.noShow.10__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_halikuwa_anyamaze-halikuwa-kutokana"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.addsub:10..80.rand.ADD-2D-V.9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946800253833","data":{"timestamp":" 946800253833"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_083053"," gameId":" 7c9cf606-5ff1-4309-b339-542ce41db36f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.addsub_10..80.rand.ADD-2D-V.9"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_75_75-78-64"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 75"," userResponse":" 75"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.addsub:10..80.rand.ADD-2D-V.9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946800260256","data":{"timestamp":" 946800260255"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_083053"," gameId":" 7c9cf606-5ff1-4309-b339-542ce41db36f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.addsub_10..80.rand.ADD-2D-V.9"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_75_75-78-64"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_43","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946800268216","data":{"timestamp":" 946800268216"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_083053"," gameId":" 7c9cf606-5ff1-4309-b339-542ce41db36f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.addsub_10..80.rand.ADD-2D-V.9"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_75_75-78-64"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946800274694","data":{"timestamp":" 946800274694"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_083053"," gameId":" 7c9cf606-5ff1-4309-b339-542ce41db36f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.addsub_10..80.rand.ADD-2D-V.9"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_75_75-78-64"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946800288863","data":{"timestamp":" 946800288862"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_083053"," gameId":" 7c9cf606-5ff1-4309-b339-542ce41db36f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.addsub_10..80.rand.ADD-2D-V.9"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_75_75-78-64"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.addsub:10..80.rand.ADD-2D-V.9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946800298732","data":{"timestamp":" 946800298732"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_083053"," gameId":" 7c9cf606-5ff1-4309-b339-542ce41db36f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.addsub_10..80.rand.ADD-2D-V.9"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_75_75-78-64"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:nonwrd.8.lc.rand.stat.show.5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946800312306","data":{"timestamp":" 946800312305"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_083053"," gameId":" 7c9cf606-5ff1-4309-b339-542ce41db36f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.addsub_10..80.rand.ADD-2D-V.9"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_75_75-78-64"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946800319905","data":{"timestamp":" 946800319904"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_083053"," gameId":" 7c9cf606-5ff1-4309-b339-542ce41db36f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.addsub_10..80.rand.ADD-2D-V.9"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_75_75-78-64"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946800328928","data":{"timestamp":" 946800328927"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_083053"," gameId":" 7c9cf606-5ff1-4309-b339-542ce41db36f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.addsub_10..80.rand.ADD-2D-V.9"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_75_75-78-64"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"place.value:pv-11..99.2D.diff1.8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946800336105","data":{"timestamp":" 946800336105"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_083053"," gameId":" 161b2708-36a5-4dbc-9890-1a64890a28a9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" countingx"," tutorId":" place.value_pv-11..99.2D.diff1.8"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" 1"," taskName":"  Two digit place value "," problemName":" 73"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" START"," userResponse":" START"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 5"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" tap"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"place.value:pv-11..99.2D.diff1.8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946800337221","data":{"timestamp":" 946800337221"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_083053"," gameId":" 161b2708-36a5-4dbc-9890-1a64890a28a9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" countingx"," tutorId":" place.value_pv-11..99.2D.diff1.8"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" 1"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" 73"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946800337280","data":{"timestamp":" 946800337280"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_083053"," gameId":" 161b2708-36a5-4dbc-9890-1a64890a28a9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" countingx"," tutorId":" place.value_pv-11..99.2D.diff1.8"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" 1"," taskName":"  Two digit place value "," problemName":" 73"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" ENDPROBLEM"," userResponse":" ENDPROBLEM"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 5"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" ENDPROBLEM"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:nonwrd.8.lc.rand.stat.noShow.6__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946800350921","data":{"timestamp":" 946800350921"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_083053"," gameId":" 161b2708-36a5-4dbc-9890-1a64890a28a9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" countingx"," tutorId":" place.value_pv-11..99.2D.diff1.8"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" 1"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" 73"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946800356054","data":{"timestamp":" 946800356054"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_083053"," gameId":" 161b2708-36a5-4dbc-9890-1a64890a28a9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" countingx"," tutorId":" place.value_pv-11..99.2D.diff1.8"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" 1"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" 73"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946800368021","data":{"timestamp":" 946800368021"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_083053"," gameId":" e8a9d496-9fb4-4610-a22d-699074293e17"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_46"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Akai alipokuwa mdogo mamake alizoea kumweka akilalia mkeka maridadi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AKAI"," userResponse":" AKAI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946800369210","data":{"timestamp":" 946800369210"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_083053"," gameId":" e8a9d496-9fb4-4610-a22d-699074293e17"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_46"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Akai alipokuwa mdogo mamake alizoea kumweka akilalia mkeka maridadi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIPOKUWA"," userResponse":" ALIPOKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946800370115","data":{"timestamp":" 946800370115"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_083053"," gameId":" e8a9d496-9fb4-4610-a22d-699074293e17"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_46"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Akai alipokuwa mdogo mamake alizoea kumweka akilalia mkeka maridadi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MDOGO"," userResponse":" MDOGO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946800371189","data":{"timestamp":" 946800371189"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_083053"," gameId":" e8a9d496-9fb4-4610-a22d-699074293e17"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_46"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Akai alipokuwa mdogo mamake alizoea kumweka akilalia mkeka maridadi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAMAKE"," userResponse":" MAMAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946800372193","data":{"timestamp":" 946800372193"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_083053"," gameId":" e8a9d496-9fb4-4610-a22d-699074293e17"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_46"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Akai alipokuwa mdogo mamake alizoea kumweka akilalia mkeka maridadi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIZOEA"," userResponse":" ALIZOEA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946800373047","data":{"timestamp":" 946800373047"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_083053"," gameId":" e8a9d496-9fb4-4610-a22d-699074293e17"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_46"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Akai alipokuwa mdogo mamake alizoea kumweka akilalia mkeka maridadi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUMWEKA"," userResponse":" KUMWEKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946800374155","data":{"timestamp":" 946800374155"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_083053"," gameId":" e8a9d496-9fb4-4610-a22d-699074293e17"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_46"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Akai alipokuwa mdogo mamake alizoea kumweka akilalia mkeka maridadi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AKILALIA"," userResponse":" AKILALIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946800374809","data":{"timestamp":" 946800374809"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_083053"," gameId":" e8a9d496-9fb4-4610-a22d-699074293e17"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_46"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Akai alipokuwa mdogo mamake alizoea kumweka akilalia mkeka maridadi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MKEKA"," userResponse":" MKEKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946800376110","data":{"timestamp":" 946800376110"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_083053"," gameId":" e8a9d496-9fb4-4610-a22d-699074293e17"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_46"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Akai alipokuwa mdogo mamake alizoea kumweka akilalia mkeka maridadi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MARIDADI"," userResponse":" MARIDADI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946800381318","data":{"timestamp":" 946800381318"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_083053"," gameId":" e8a9d496-9fb4-4610-a22d-699074293e17"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_46"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Akai alipokuwa mdogo mamake alizoea kumweka akilalia mkeka maridadi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AKAI"," userResponse":" AKAI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946800387777","data":{"timestamp":" 946800387777"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_083053"," gameId":" e8a9d496-9fb4-4610-a22d-699074293e17"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_46"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Akai alipokuwa mdogo mamake alizoea kumweka akilalia mkeka maridadi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ALIPOKUWA"," userResponse":" START_ALIPOKUWA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946800388816","data":{"timestamp":" 946800388815"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_083053"," gameId":" e8a9d496-9fb4-4610-a22d-699074293e17"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_46"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Akai alipokuwa mdogo mamake alizoea kumweka akilalia mkeka maridadi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" ALIPOKUWA"," userResponse":" MDOGO"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946800390762","data":{"timestamp":" 946800390762"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_083053"," gameId":" e8a9d496-9fb4-4610-a22d-699074293e17"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_46"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Akai alipokuwa mdogo mamake alizoea kumweka akilalia mkeka maridadi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIPOKUWA"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946800391917","data":{"timestamp":" 946800391917"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_083053"," gameId":" e8a9d496-9fb4-4610-a22d-699074293e17"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_46"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Akai alipokuwa mdogo mamake alizoea kumweka akilalia mkeka maridadi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MDOGO"," userResponse":" START_MAMAKE"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946800393527","data":{"timestamp":" 946800393527"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_083053"," gameId":" e8a9d496-9fb4-4610-a22d-699074293e17"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_46"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Akai alipokuwa mdogo mamake alizoea kumweka akilalia mkeka maridadi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" MDOGO"," userResponse":" START_MAMAKE"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946800395198","data":{"timestamp":" 946800395198"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_083053"," gameId":" e8a9d496-9fb4-4610-a22d-699074293e17"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_46"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Akai alipokuwa mdogo mamake alizoea kumweka akilalia mkeka maridadi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MDOGO"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946800397356","data":{"timestamp":" 946800397356"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_083053"," gameId":" e8a9d496-9fb4-4610-a22d-699074293e17"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_46"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Akai alipokuwa mdogo mamake alizoea kumweka akilalia mkeka maridadi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAMAKE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946800399439","data":{"timestamp":" 946800399438"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_083053"," gameId":" e8a9d496-9fb4-4610-a22d-699074293e17"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_46"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Akai alipokuwa mdogo mamake alizoea kumweka akilalia mkeka maridadi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946800399552","data":{"timestamp":" 946800399552"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_083053"," gameId":" e8a9d496-9fb4-4610-a22d-699074293e17"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_46"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Akai alipokuwa mdogo mamake alizoea kumweka akilalia mkeka maridadi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAMAKE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bigmath:add.by.rand.10..89.AllCarryBorrow.lev11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946800460212","data":{"timestamp":" 946800460212"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_083053"," gameId":" 654a0290-2051-498f-a600-f4f98e33cbac"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bigmath"," tutorId":" bigmath_add.by.rand.10..89.AllCarryBorrow.lev11"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" demo"," taskName":"  Double digit Carry"," problemName":" bigmath_13+79=92"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" 2"," userResponse":" 1"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bigmath:add.by.rand.10..89.AllCarryBorrow.lev11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946800480958","data":{"timestamp":" 946800480958"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_083053"," gameId":" 654a0290-2051-498f-a600-f4f98e33cbac"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bigmath"," tutorId":" bigmath_add.by.rand.10..89.AllCarryBorrow.lev11"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" demo"," taskName":"  Double digit Carry"," problemName":" bigmath_13+79=92"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" 2"," userResponse":" 0"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bigmath:add.by.rand.10..89.AllCarryBorrow.lev11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946800584182","data":{"timestamp":" 946800584182"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_083053"," gameId":" 654a0290-2051-498f-a600-f4f98e33cbac"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bigmath"," tutorId":" bigmath_add.by.rand.10..89.AllCarryBorrow.lev11"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" demo"," taskName":"  Double digit Carry"," problemName":" bigmath_13+79=92"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" 2"," userResponse":" 2"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bigmath:add.by.rand.10..89.AllCarryBorrow.lev11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946800598292","data":{"timestamp":" 946800598292"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_083053"," gameId":" 654a0290-2051-498f-a600-f4f98e33cbac"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bigmath"," tutorId":" bigmath_add.by.rand.10..89.AllCarryBorrow.lev11"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" demo"," taskName":"  Double digit Carry"," problemName":" bigmath_13+79=92"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" 2"," userResponse":" 2"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bigmath:add.by.rand.10..89.AllCarryBorrow.lev11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946800619579","data":{"timestamp":" 946800619578"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_083053"," gameId":" 654a0290-2051-498f-a600-f4f98e33cbac"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bigmath"," tutorId":" bigmath_add.by.rand.10..89.AllCarryBorrow.lev11"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" demo"," taskName":"  Double digit Carry"," problemName":" bigmath_13+79=92"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" 2"," userResponse":" 9"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bigmath:add.by.rand.10..89.AllCarryBorrow.lev11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946800628329","data":{"timestamp":" 946800628328"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_083053"," gameId":" 654a0290-2051-498f-a600-f4f98e33cbac"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bigmath"," tutorId":" bigmath_add.by.rand.10..89.AllCarryBorrow.lev11"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" demo"," taskName":"  Double digit Carry"," problemName":" bigmath_13+79=92"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" 2"," userResponse":" 2"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bigmath:add.by.rand.10..89.AllCarryBorrow.lev11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946800637977","data":{"timestamp":" 946800637977"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_083053"," gameId":" 654a0290-2051-498f-a600-f4f98e33cbac"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bigmath"," tutorId":" bigmath_add.by.rand.10..89.AllCarryBorrow.lev11"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" demo"," taskName":"  Double digit Carry"," problemName":" bigmath_13+79=92"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" 1"," userResponse":" 9"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bigmath:add.by.rand.10..89.AllCarryBorrow.lev11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946800656074","data":{"timestamp":" 946800656074"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_083053"," gameId":" 654a0290-2051-498f-a600-f4f98e33cbac"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bigmath"," tutorId":" bigmath_add.by.rand.10..89.AllCarryBorrow.lev11"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" demo"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" bigmath_13+79=92"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946800662191","data":{"timestamp":" 946800662191"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_083053"," gameId":" 654a0290-2051-498f-a600-f4f98e33cbac"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bigmath"," tutorId":" bigmath_add.by.rand.10..89.AllCarryBorrow.lev11"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" demo"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" bigmath_13+79=92"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946800668980","data":{"timestamp":" 946800668979"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_083053"," gameId":" 654a0290-2051-498f-a600-f4f98e33cbac"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bigmath"," tutorId":" bigmath_add.by.rand.10..89.AllCarryBorrow.lev11"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" demo"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" bigmath_13+79=92"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946800684195","data":{"timestamp":" 946800684194"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_083053"," gameId":" d65e0cd0-ef87-4ce5-8300-9cdd27950a67"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_47"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sakima aliishi na wazazi wake na dada yake wa miaka minne."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SAKIMA"," userResponse":" SAKIMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946800685198","data":{"timestamp":" 946800685198"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_083053"," gameId":" d65e0cd0-ef87-4ce5-8300-9cdd27950a67"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_47"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sakima aliishi na wazazi wake na dada yake wa miaka minne."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIISHI"," userResponse":" ALIISHI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946800685389","data":{"timestamp":" 946800685389"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_083053"," gameId":" d65e0cd0-ef87-4ce5-8300-9cdd27950a67"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_47"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sakima aliishi na wazazi wake na dada yake wa miaka minne."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946800685635","data":{"timestamp":" 946800685635"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_083053"," gameId":" d65e0cd0-ef87-4ce5-8300-9cdd27950a67"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_47"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Sakima aliishi na wazazi wake na dada yake wa miaka minne."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946800685720","data":{"timestamp":" 946800685720"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_083053"," gameId":" d65e0cd0-ef87-4ce5-8300-9cdd27950a67"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_47"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sakima aliishi na wazazi wake na dada yake wa miaka minne."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bigmath:add.by.rand.10..89.AllCarryBorrow.lev11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946800705545","data":{"timestamp":" 946800705545"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_083053"," gameId":" ddc62b93-41cc-4c45-ac1d-fac41067d885"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bigmath"," tutorId":" bigmath_add.by.rand.10..89.AllCarryBorrow.lev11"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" demo"," taskName":"  Double digit Carry"," problemName":" bigmath_13+79=92"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" 2"," userResponse":" 2"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bigmath:add.by.rand.10..89.AllCarryBorrow.lev11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946800720210","data":{"timestamp":" 946800720210"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_083053"," gameId":" ddc62b93-41cc-4c45-ac1d-fac41067d885"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bigmath"," tutorId":" bigmath_add.by.rand.10..89.AllCarryBorrow.lev11"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" demo"," taskName":"  Double digit Carry"," problemName":" bigmath_13+79=92"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" 1"," userResponse":" 8"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bigmath:add.by.rand.10..89.AllCarryBorrow.lev11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946800726534","data":{"timestamp":" 946800726534"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_083053"," gameId":" ddc62b93-41cc-4c45-ac1d-fac41067d885"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bigmath"," tutorId":" bigmath_add.by.rand.10..89.AllCarryBorrow.lev11"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" demo"," taskName":"  Double digit Carry"," problemName":" bigmath_13+79=92"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" 1"," userResponse":" 8"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bigmath:add.by.rand.10..89.AllCarryBorrow.lev11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946800731801","data":{"timestamp":" 946800731801"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_083053"," gameId":" ddc62b93-41cc-4c45-ac1d-fac41067d885"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bigmath"," tutorId":" bigmath_add.by.rand.10..89.AllCarryBorrow.lev11"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" demo"," taskName":"  Double digit Carry"," problemName":" bigmath_13+79=92"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" 1"," userResponse":" 7"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bigmath:add.by.rand.10..89.AllCarryBorrow.lev11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946800737868","data":{"timestamp":" 946800737868"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_083053"," gameId":" ddc62b93-41cc-4c45-ac1d-fac41067d885"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bigmath"," tutorId":" bigmath_add.by.rand.10..89.AllCarryBorrow.lev11"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" demo"," taskName":"  Double digit Carry"," problemName":" bigmath_13+79=92"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" 1"," userResponse":" 8"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bigmath:add.by.rand.10..89.AllCarryBorrow.lev11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946800743220","data":{"timestamp":" 946800743220"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_083053"," gameId":" ddc62b93-41cc-4c45-ac1d-fac41067d885"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bigmath"," tutorId":" bigmath_add.by.rand.10..89.AllCarryBorrow.lev11"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" demo"," taskName":"  Double digit Carry"," problemName":" bigmath_13+79=92"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" 1"," userResponse":" 9"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bigmath:add.by.rand.10..89.AllCarryBorrow.lev11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946800755341","data":{"timestamp":" 946800755340"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_083053"," gameId":" ddc62b93-41cc-4c45-ac1d-fac41067d885"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bigmath"," tutorId":" bigmath_add.by.rand.10..89.AllCarryBorrow.lev11"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" demo"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" bigmath_13+79=92"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::nonwrd.len-8.rand.6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946800766783","data":{"timestamp":" 946800766783"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_083053"," gameId":" 3e9f93a1-d6a7-4bea-88cc-d391e519818a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__nonwrd.len-8.rand.6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" nijujuwa"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NIJUJUWA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::nonwrd.len-8.rand.6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946800766836","data":{"timestamp":" 946800766836"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_083053"," gameId":" 3e9f93a1-d6a7-4bea-88cc-d391e519818a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__nonwrd.len-8.rand.6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" nijujuwa"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946800766975","data":{"timestamp":" 946800766975"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_083053"," gameId":" 3e9f93a1-d6a7-4bea-88cc-d391e519818a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__nonwrd.len-8.rand.6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" nijujuwa"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NIJUJUWA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946800771538","data":{"timestamp":" 946800771538"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_083053"," gameId":" 3e9f93a1-d6a7-4bea-88cc-d391e519818a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__nonwrd.len-8.rand.6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" nijujuwa"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946800781619","data":{"timestamp":" 946800781619"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_083053"," gameId":" 3e9f93a1-d6a7-4bea-88cc-d391e519818a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__nonwrd.len-8.rand.6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" nijujuwa"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"num.scale:72..82.off1.11__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946800789664","data":{"timestamp":" 946800789663"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_083053"," gameId":" 3e9f93a1-d6a7-4bea-88cc-d391e519818a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__nonwrd.len-8.rand.6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" nijujuwa"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946800795230","data":{"timestamp":" 946800795230"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000102_083053"," gameId":" 3e9f93a1-d6a7-4bea-88cc-d391e519818a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__nonwrd.len-8.rand.6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" nijujuwa"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"end":"end"}]}